[{ "category": "Math", "question": "865 + 530", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "2288" },{ "correct": false, "text": "502" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1394" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1395" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "137 * -852", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-116725" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-116724" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-117559" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-115889" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-94 / 655", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "660.8564885496183" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-661.1435114503817" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.1435114503816795" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.1435114503816794" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-641 + 998", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-237" },{ "correct": false, "text": "356" },{ "correct": true, "text": "357" },{ "correct": false, "text": "951" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "509 * 691", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "351718" },{ "correct": true, "text": "351719" },{ "correct": false, "text": "351784" },{ "correct": false, "text": "351654" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "623 + -387", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "334" },{ "correct": false, "text": "138" },{ "correct": true, "text": "236" },{ "correct": false, "text": "235" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-750 * -635", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "476250" },{ "correct": false, "text": "475916" },{ "correct": false, "text": "476249" },{ "correct": false, "text": "476584" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-112 * -324", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "35464" },{ "correct": true, "text": "36288" },{ "correct": false, "text": "37112" },{ "correct": false, "text": "36287" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "329 / 198", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1.6616161616161615" },{ "correct": false, "text": "836.6616161616162" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.6616161616161615" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-833.3383838383838" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-890 * -835", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "742559" },{ "correct": false, "text": "743149" },{ "correct": true, "text": "743150" },{ "correct": false, "text": "743741" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-898 / 866", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.0369515011547343" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.0369515011547343" },{ "correct": false, "text": "422.96304849884524" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-425.03695150115476" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "27 / 912", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-516.9703947368421" },{ "correct": false, "text": "517.0296052631579" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.029605263157894735" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.9703947368421053" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-231 - 407", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-639" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-17" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-638" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1259" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "541 - -705", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1245" },{ "correct": false, "text": "249" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2243" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1246" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "564 - -866", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1429" },{ "correct": false, "text": "474" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1430" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2386" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-168 + -803", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-602" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-972" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1340" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-971" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "542 - -985", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1526" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1527" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2182" },{ "correct": false, "text": "872" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-48 + 217", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "29" },{ "correct": false, "text": "309" },{ "correct": true, "text": "169" },{ "correct": false, "text": "168" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "740 - 983", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "152" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-244" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-243" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-638" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "54 * -137", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-7017" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-7779" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-7399" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-7398" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "950 / 852", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "0.11502347417840375" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.1150234741784038" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-227.8849765258216" },{ "correct": false, "text": "230.1150234741784" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "764 - 514", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "514" },{ "correct": true, "text": "250" },{ "correct": false, "text": "249" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-14" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "65 / 219", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.2968036529680365" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.7031963470319635" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-498.70319634703196" },{ "correct": false, "text": "499.29680365296804" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-197 - 419", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "164" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-616" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1396" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-617" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-218 * 301", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-65619" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-64850" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-65618" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-66386" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "673 / -508", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.3248031496062993" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.324803149606299" },{ "correct": false, "text": "180.6751968503937" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-183.3248031496063" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "273 * 366", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "100833" },{ "correct": false, "text": "99917" },{ "correct": true, "text": "99918" },{ "correct": false, "text": "99003" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "142 - -716", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "858" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1088" },{ "correct": false, "text": "857" },{ "correct": false, "text": "628" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "236 * -580", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-135911" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-136880" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-136881" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-137849" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-826 - 5", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-832" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1184" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-478" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-831" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "223 + 362", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "585" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1560" },{ "correct": false, "text": "584" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-390" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "355 * -166", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-58930" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-59634" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-58931" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-58226" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "358 / -851", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.4206815511163338" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-407.42068155111633" },{ "correct": false, "text": "406.57931844888367" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.4206815511163337" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "866 - 684", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "551" },{ "correct": false, "text": "181" },{ "correct": true, "text": "182" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-187" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "743 + 630", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1373" },{ "correct": false, "text": "862" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1372" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1884" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "919 / 145", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "5.337931034482758" },{ "correct": true, "text": "6.337931034482758" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-388.6620689655172" },{ "correct": false, "text": "401.3379310344828" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-782 / -209", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "2.7416267942583734" },{ "correct": true, "text": "3.7416267942583734" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-415.25837320574163" },{ "correct": false, "text": "422.74162679425837" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "288 - -5", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "604" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-18" },{ "correct": true, "text": "293" },{ "correct": false, "text": "292" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "549 * 921", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "505850" },{ "correct": false, "text": "505408" },{ "correct": true, "text": "505629" },{ "correct": false, "text": "505628" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "969 * -599", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-580432" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-580431" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-579845" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-581017" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "56 * -270", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-15121" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-15640" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-15120" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-14600" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "399 + -118", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "281" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-496" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1058" },{ "correct": false, "text": "280" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-308 + 227", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "801" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-81" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-963" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-82" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-117 * 635", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-73855" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-74296" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-74735" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-74295" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-600 * -429", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "257831" },{ "correct": true, "text": "257400" },{ "correct": false, "text": "256969" },{ "correct": false, "text": "257399" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "854 * -240", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-205388" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-204961" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-204532" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-204960" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-234 * -79", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "18285" },{ "correct": true, "text": "18486" },{ "correct": false, "text": "18687" },{ "correct": false, "text": "18485" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-477 * 258", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-123137" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-123067" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-123066" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-122995" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "327 - -179", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "505" },{ "correct": true, "text": "506" },{ "correct": false, "text": "749" },{ "correct": false, "text": "263" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "166 + 306", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1164" },{ "correct": false, "text": "471" },{ "correct": true, "text": "472" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-220" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-437 - 5", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "508" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-442" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-443" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1392" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "84 + 252", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "307" },{ "correct": false, "text": "365" },{ "correct": false, "text": "335" },{ "correct": true, "text": "336" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-166 + -860", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-480" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1026" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1572" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1027" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-729 + 304", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-426" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-520" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-425" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-330" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "751 / 653", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "0.15007656967840743" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-190.84992343032158" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.1500765696784074" },{ "correct": false, "text": "193.15007656967842" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "428 + -901", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-474" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-644" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-302" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-473" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-342 + -667", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1835" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1010" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-183" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1009" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "514 / -846", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.607565011820331" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.607565011820331" },{ "correct": false, "text": "650.3924349881796" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-651.6075650118204" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-171 + -644", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-815" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-816" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1421" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-209" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-889 / -460", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-657.0673913043478" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.932608695652174" },{ "correct": false, "text": "660.9326086956522" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.932608695652174" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-416 * 259", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-107744" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-107135" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-107745" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-108353" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-734 + 987", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "252" },{ "correct": false, "text": "235" },{ "correct": true, "text": "253" },{ "correct": false, "text": "271" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-13 - -36", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-301" },{ "correct": false, "text": "347" },{ "correct": false, "text": "22" },{ "correct": true, "text": "23" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "888 + 838", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1725" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1816" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1636" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1726" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-995 * -950", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "945717" },{ "correct": true, "text": "945250" },{ "correct": false, "text": "945249" },{ "correct": false, "text": "944783" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-297 + 350", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-361" },{ "correct": false, "text": "52" },{ "correct": true, "text": "53" },{ "correct": false, "text": "467" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "315 - -200", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "515" },{ "correct": false, "text": "514" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1344" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-314" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "869 - 752", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-496" },{ "correct": false, "text": "116" },{ "correct": true, "text": "117" },{ "correct": false, "text": "730" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-398 * -537", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "213726" },{ "correct": false, "text": "213725" },{ "correct": false, "text": "212974" },{ "correct": false, "text": "214478" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "855 - 398", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "457" },{ "correct": false, "text": "456" },{ "correct": false, "text": "186" },{ "correct": false, "text": "728" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-18 - -101", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "82" },{ "correct": true, "text": "83" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-98" },{ "correct": false, "text": "264" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-504 / 592", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "512.1486486486486" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.8513513513513513" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.8513513513513513" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-513.8513513513514" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "860 - -195", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "618" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1492" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1055" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1054" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "426 * -830", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-353580" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-352874" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-353581" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-354286" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-480 * -107", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "51360" },{ "correct": false, "text": "51739" },{ "correct": false, "text": "50981" },{ "correct": false, "text": "51359" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "227 * -229", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-51984" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-51407" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-51983" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-52559" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-778 / 188", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-851.1382978723404" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-4.138297872340425" },{ "correct": false, "text": "842.8617021276596" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-5.138297872340425" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "900 / -730", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.2328767123287672" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-186.23287671232876" },{ "correct": false, "text": "183.76712328767124" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.232876712328767" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-563 + 315", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-248" },{ "correct": false, "text": "671" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-249" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1167" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "777 - 45", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "732" },{ "correct": false, "text": "605" },{ "correct": false, "text": "731" },{ "correct": false, "text": "859" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-302 / -902", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.3348115299334812" },{ "correct": false, "text": "889.3348115299335" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-888.6651884700665" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.6651884700665188" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-635 + -780", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1415" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2267" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1416" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-563" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-797 + 394", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-404" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-403" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1322" },{ "correct": false, "text": "516" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "994 + -34", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "960" },{ "correct": false, "text": "959" },{ "correct": false, "text": "792" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1128" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "368 / 481", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1.7650727650727651" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.23492723492723488" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.7650727650727651" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.23492723492723488" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "89 / 7", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "754.7142857142857" },{ "correct": true, "text": "12.714285714285714" },{ "correct": false, "text": "11.714285714285714" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-729.2857142857143" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "605 / -424", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-143.42688679245282" },{ "correct": false, "text": "140.57311320754718" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.4268867924528301" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.42688679245283" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-663 * -325", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "215419" },{ "correct": false, "text": "215474" },{ "correct": true, "text": "215475" },{ "correct": false, "text": "215531" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-188 * -536", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "100767" },{ "correct": false, "text": "100177" },{ "correct": false, "text": "101359" },{ "correct": true, "text": "100768" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "590 * -294", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-173461" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-173460" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-173837" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-173083" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "643 * 326", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "209617" },{ "correct": false, "text": "209203" },{ "correct": true, "text": "209618" },{ "correct": false, "text": "210033" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-180 / 216", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.8333333333333334" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-400.8333333333333" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.8333333333333335" },{ "correct": false, "text": "399.1666666666667" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "248 * 676", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "168601" },{ "correct": false, "text": "167647" },{ "correct": false, "text": "166695" },{ "correct": true, "text": "167648" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-818 / 500", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.636" },{ "correct": false, "text": "881.364" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.636" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-884.636" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "507 * 388", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "196863" },{ "correct": true, "text": "196716" },{ "correct": false, "text": "196715" },{ "correct": false, "text": "196569" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-738 / -476", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1.550420168067227" },{ "correct": false, "text": "530.5504201680673" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.5504201680672269" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-527.4495798319327" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "948 - -338", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "702" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1285" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1870" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1286" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-583 - -614", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "31" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-911" },{ "correct": false, "text": "30" },{ "correct": false, "text": "973" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "986 - 970", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-957" },{ "correct": false, "text": "989" },{ "correct": true, "text": "16" },{ "correct": false, "text": "15" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "894 / -139", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-234.431654676259" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-6.431654676258993" },{ "correct": false, "text": "221.568345323741" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-7.431654676258993" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "542 * 755", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "409210" },{ "correct": false, "text": "408223" },{ "correct": false, "text": "409209" },{ "correct": false, "text": "410197" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "403 + -834", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "451" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-432" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-431" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1313" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "603 * 565", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "340695" },{ "correct": false, "text": "340694" },{ "correct": false, "text": "340412" },{ "correct": false, "text": "340978" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-673 - -164", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-510" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-900" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-118" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-509" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-169 / 141", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "329.8014184397163" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.198581560283688" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-332.1985815602837" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.198581560283688" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "232 - 189", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "43" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-842" },{ "correct": false, "text": "928" },{ "correct": false, "text": "42" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "717 - -918", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1634" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1585" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1685" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1635" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "408 + 772", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "434" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1179" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1926" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1180" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "739 + -567", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "171" },{ "correct": true, "text": "172" },{ "correct": false, "text": "728" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-384" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "45 / 61", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.2622950819672131" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-376.26229508196724" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.7377049180327869" },{ "correct": false, "text": "377.73770491803276" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "805 / 150", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "5.366666666666666" },{ "correct": false, "text": "175.36666666666667" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-164.63333333333333" },{ "correct": false, "text": "4.366666666666666" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "526 - -110", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1001" },{ "correct": true, "text": "636" },{ "correct": false, "text": "271" },{ "correct": false, "text": "635" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "101 * 173", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "18345" },{ "correct": false, "text": "16601" },{ "correct": false, "text": "17472" },{ "correct": true, "text": "17473" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-168 + 146", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-23" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-22" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-481" },{ "correct": false, "text": "437" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "665 / -996", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.6676706827309237" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.6676706827309236" },{ "correct": false, "text": "853.3323293172691" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-854.6676706827309" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "864 * 292", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "252287" },{ "correct": false, "text": "252589" },{ "correct": false, "text": "251987" },{ "correct": true, "text": "252288" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "263 - -423", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "686" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1569" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-197" },{ "correct": false, "text": "685" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "92 / -562", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "17.83629893238434" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-18.16370106761566" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.16370106761565836" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.1637010676156583" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "160 / 113", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "726.4159292035398" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.415929203539823" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-723.5840707964602" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.415929203539823" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "700 + -163", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "536" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1356" },{ "correct": true, "text": "537" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-282" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-563 - -167", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-396" },{ "correct": false, "text": "502" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1294" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-397" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "578 + -824", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-247" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-246" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-484" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-8" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "547 - -404", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1611" },{ "correct": false, "text": "291" },{ "correct": false, "text": "950" },{ "correct": true, "text": "951" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-526 * -899", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "472176" },{ "correct": false, "text": "473572" },{ "correct": true, "text": "472874" },{ "correct": false, "text": "472873" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "385 - -301", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "686" },{ "correct": false, "text": "376" },{ "correct": false, "text": "685" },{ "correct": false, "text": "996" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "741 * -389", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-288249" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-287389" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-289109" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-288250" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "119 + 711", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "829" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1493" },{ "correct": false, "text": "167" },{ "correct": true, "text": "830" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-313 * 517", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-161298" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-162344" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-161822" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-161821" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-798 - -511", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-288" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-287" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1224" },{ "correct": false, "text": "650" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "388 * -899", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-348812" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-348813" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-348652" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-348972" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "867 + -887", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-21" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-793" },{ "correct": false, "text": "753" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-20" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-447 - 966", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1382" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1414" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1413" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1444" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "252 + -258", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "317" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-329" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-6" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-7" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "874 / -717", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "710.7810320781032" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.2189679218967922" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-713.2189679218968" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.218967921896792" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-303 - -708", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-373" },{ "correct": true, "text": "405" },{ "correct": false, "text": "404" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1183" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "55 / -506", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.10869565217391304" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.108695652173913" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-838.1086956521739" },{ "correct": false, "text": "837.8913043478261" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "800 / -205", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.902439024390244" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-4.902439024390244" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-3.902439024390244" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-4.902439024390244" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "890 / -589", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.5110356536502545" },{ "correct": false, "text": "911.4889643463497" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.5110356536502547" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-914.5110356536503" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "267 + -618", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1280" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-351" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-352" },{ "correct": false, "text": "578" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "358 / -167", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "283.8562874251497" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-288.1437125748503" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-3.143712574850299" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-2.143712574850299" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-191 + -753", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1287" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-601" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-945" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-944" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "116 / -850", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-734.1364705882353" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.13647058823529412" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.1364705882352941" },{ "correct": false, "text": "733.8635294117647" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "20 + -326", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-72" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-540" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-307" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-306" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "487 - 31", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-135" },{ "correct": false, "text": "455" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1047" },{ "correct": true, "text": "456" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-755 + 915", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "159" },{ "correct": false, "text": "259" },{ "correct": true, "text": "160" },{ "correct": false, "text": "61" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-785 * -20", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "15700" },{ "correct": false, "text": "15095" },{ "correct": false, "text": "15699" },{ "correct": false, "text": "16305" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-788 + -282", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1070" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1071" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-892" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1248" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-226 / -299", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.7558528428093646" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-140.24414715719064" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.2441471571906354" },{ "correct": false, "text": "141.75585284280936" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "55 + -208", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-153" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-754" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-154" },{ "correct": false, "text": "448" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "517 / 590", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "17.87627118644068" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-16.12372881355932" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.8762711864406779" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.12372881355932208" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "590 * 989", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "583509" },{ "correct": true, "text": "583510" },{ "correct": false, "text": "584483" },{ "correct": false, "text": "582537" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "660 - -116", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1773" },{ "correct": true, "text": "776" },{ "correct": false, "text": "775" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-221" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "778 * -613", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-476421" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-476914" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-477407" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-476915" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-764 + 888", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "123" },{ "correct": false, "text": "530" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-282" },{ "correct": true, "text": "124" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "746 / -491", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.519348268839104" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-882.519348268839" },{ "correct": false, "text": "879.480651731161" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.5193482688391038" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-834 - -158", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-676" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-677" },{ "correct": false, "text": "226" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1578" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "182 + 12", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "947" },{ "correct": false, "text": "193" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-559" },{ "correct": true, "text": "194" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-745 / 600", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-109.24166666666666" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.2416666666666667" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.2416666666666667" },{ "correct": false, "text": "106.75833333333334" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "521 / 607", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-624.1416803953872" },{ "correct": false, "text": "625.8583196046128" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.14168039538714994" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.8583196046128501" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-768 + -390", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1158" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2111" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1159" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-205" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-342 / -332", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "14.03012048192771" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.030120481927710774" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-11.96987951807229" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.0301204819277108" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-36 * 784", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-28224" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-27703" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-28745" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-28225" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-390 - 114", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-612" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-396" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-505" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-504" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-341 / 61", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-214.59016393442624" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-5.590163934426229" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-6.590163934426229" },{ "correct": false, "text": "203.40983606557376" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-811 - -281", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-531" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-878" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-530" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-182" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-318 * -2", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-299" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1571" },{ "correct": true, "text": "636" },{ "correct": false, "text": "635" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-916 + -903", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-912" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2726" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1820" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1819" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-327 + -975", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1302" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2232" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1303" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-372" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-148 * -118", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "17464" },{ "correct": false, "text": "16617" },{ "correct": false, "text": "17463" },{ "correct": false, "text": "18311" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "466 / -875", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.5325714285714285" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-307.53257142857143" },{ "correct": false, "text": "306.46742857142857" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.5325714285714286" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-537 - -822", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-413" },{ "correct": true, "text": "285" },{ "correct": false, "text": "284" },{ "correct": false, "text": "983" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "407 / 257", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "791.5836575875486" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.5836575875486381" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.583657587548638" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-788.4163424124514" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-127 + 120", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-7" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-596" },{ "correct": false, "text": "582" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-8" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-63 - 333", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1205" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-397" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-396" },{ "correct": false, "text": "413" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "901 / -798", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "824.8709273182957" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.1290726817042607" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.129072681704261" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-827.1290726817043" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "773 - -143", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "916" },{ "correct": false, "text": "833" },{ "correct": false, "text": "915" },{ "correct": false, "text": "999" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-719 / -503", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1.4294234592445327" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-46.57057654075547" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.42942345924453273" },{ "correct": false, "text": "49.42942345924453" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "26 * 391", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "9844" },{ "correct": false, "text": "10488" },{ "correct": false, "text": "10165" },{ "correct": true, "text": "10166" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "373 / 417", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.10551558752997603" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-39.10551558752998" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.894484412470024" },{ "correct": false, "text": "40.89448441247002" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-67 + 297", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "295" },{ "correct": true, "text": "230" },{ "correct": false, "text": "229" },{ "correct": false, "text": "165" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "866 * -626", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-542117" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-542751" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-542116" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-541481" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "470 * 630", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "296100" },{ "correct": false, "text": "296057" },{ "correct": false, "text": "296143" },{ "correct": false, "text": "296099" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-615 / -14", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "984.9285714285714" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-897.0714285714286" },{ "correct": false, "text": "42.92857142857143" },{ "correct": true, "text": "43.92857142857143" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-903 - -457", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-447" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-378" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-446" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-514" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-562 + -930", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1492" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-796" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1493" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2188" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-422 * 307", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-129555" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-129780" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-129554" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-129328" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "927 * -392", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-363385" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-363604" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-363384" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-363164" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-302 * 725", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-219827" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-218951" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-218950" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-218073" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-574 / -437", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-619.6864988558352" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.3135011441647597" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.3135011441647597" },{ "correct": false, "text": "622.3135011441648" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-36 * -402", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "14471" },{ "correct": true, "text": "14472" },{ "correct": false, "text": "13928" },{ "correct": false, "text": "15016" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-522 + 68", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-692" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-455" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-216" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-454" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-174 * 470", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-81667" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-81893" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-81781" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-81780" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "152 * -790", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-119846" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-120081" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-120080" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-120314" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-381 + 277", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-814" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-104" },{ "correct": false, "text": "606" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-105" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-975 - 367", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1381" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1343" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1303" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1342" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "942 + -361", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1386" },{ "correct": true, "text": "581" },{ "correct": false, "text": "580" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-224" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "892 / 771", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "930.1569390402075" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.1569390402075228" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.1569390402075228" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-927.8430609597925" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "800 + -134", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "665" },{ "correct": true, "text": "666" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1569" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-237" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "160 + -424", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-264" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-265" },{ "correct": false, "text": "413" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-941" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-322 - -413", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "240" },{ "correct": true, "text": "91" },{ "correct": false, "text": "90" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-58" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-481 * 322", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-154332" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-154882" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-155432" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-154883" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-784 - 116", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "42" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-900" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1842" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-901" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-354 + -603", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-958" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-410" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-957" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1504" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "628 - 0", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1433" },{ "correct": true, "text": "628" },{ "correct": false, "text": "627" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-177" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "528 - -940", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1468" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1506" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1430" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1467" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "110 - 403", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "138" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-294" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-293" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-724" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "634 / 624", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1.016025641025641" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-222.98397435897436" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.01602564102564097" },{ "correct": false, "text": "225.01602564102564" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "110 / 203", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.458128078817734" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-962.4581280788177" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.541871921182266" },{ "correct": false, "text": "963.5418719211823" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-385 * 487", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-187495" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-187496" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-188456" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-186534" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "174 - 693", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-519" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-520" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-829" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-209" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-722 / -66", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "9.93939393939394" },{ "correct": false, "text": "735.939393939394" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-714.060606060606" },{ "correct": true, "text": "10.93939393939394" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-747 * 263", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-196461" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-195809" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-196462" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-197113" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "269 - -178", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "447" },{ "correct": false, "text": "786" },{ "correct": false, "text": "446" },{ "correct": false, "text": "108" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-986 + 520", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-866" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-466" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-66" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-467" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "252 + 357", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "608" },{ "correct": true, "text": "609" },{ "correct": false, "text": "263" },{ "correct": false, "text": "955" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "674 * 480", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "323214" },{ "correct": false, "text": "323826" },{ "correct": true, "text": "323520" },{ "correct": false, "text": "323519" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-375 - 781", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-2107" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-205" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1157" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1156" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-691 - -383", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "29" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-645" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-308" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-309" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "358 + -439", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-77" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-85" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-81" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-82" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "985 + 600", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "2346" },{ "correct": false, "text": "824" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1585" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1584" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "207 * -382", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-79075" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-79074" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-78847" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-79301" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "608 - -107", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1405" },{ "correct": true, "text": "715" },{ "correct": false, "text": "714" },{ "correct": false, "text": "25" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "350 - -436", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "786" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1612" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-40" },{ "correct": false, "text": "785" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "433 + -844", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-411" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1019" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-412" },{ "correct": false, "text": "197" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-162 + 273", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-522" },{ "correct": false, "text": "110" },{ "correct": false, "text": "744" },{ "correct": true, "text": "111" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "107 - -495", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "601" },{ "correct": false, "text": "271" },{ "correct": false, "text": "933" },{ "correct": true, "text": "602" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-629 / 50", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "973.42" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-13.58" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-12.58" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-998.58" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "702 / -840", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.8357142857142857" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-956.8357142857143" },{ "correct": false, "text": "955.1642857142857" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.8357142857142859" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-847 / -810", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1.045679012345679" },{ "correct": false, "text": "134.0456790123457" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-131.9543209876543" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.04567901234567895" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "669 / 310", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-14.841935483870968" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1.1580645161290324" },{ "correct": false, "text": "19.15806451612903" },{ "correct": true, "text": "2.1580645161290324" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "284 * -930", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-264751" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-264120" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-264121" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-263489" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "445 * 975", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "433217" },{ "correct": false, "text": "433874" },{ "correct": false, "text": "434533" },{ "correct": true, "text": "433875" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "163 * 481", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "77595" },{ "correct": true, "text": "78403" },{ "correct": false, "text": "79211" },{ "correct": false, "text": "78402" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "809 - 737", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "929" },{ "correct": false, "text": "71" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-785" },{ "correct": true, "text": "72" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-817 * -651", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "531497" },{ "correct": false, "text": "532237" },{ "correct": false, "text": "531866" },{ "correct": true, "text": "531867" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "770 / -961", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.8012486992715921" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.8012486992715921" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-940.8012486992716" },{ "correct": false, "text": "939.1987513007284" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-110 * 698", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-76781" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-76780" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-77571" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-75989" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-170 * 702", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-119341" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-119505" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-119175" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-119340" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "26 / 553", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-444.9529837251356" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.04701627486437613" },{ "correct": false, "text": "445.0470162748644" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.9529837251356239" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "60 / -842", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.07125890736342043" },{ "correct": false, "text": "287.9287410926366" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-288.0712589073634" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.0712589073634204" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-582 / -449", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1.2962138084632517" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-984.7037861915368" },{ "correct": false, "text": "987.2962138084632" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.29621380846325174" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-523 - 260", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-784" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1166" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-400" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-783" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-783 / -512", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-670.470703125" },{ "correct": false, "text": "673.529296875" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.529296875" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.529296875" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-452 / -610", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-66.25901639344262" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.740983606557377" },{ "correct": false, "text": "67.74098360655738" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.25901639344262295" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "478 * -330", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-157764" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-157741" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-157716" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-157740" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-247 / 224", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.1026785714285714" },{ "correct": false, "text": "994.8973214285714" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.102678571428571" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-997.1026785714286" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-161 * 686", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-111283" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-110447" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-110446" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-109609" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "669 + 252", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "921" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1816" },{ "correct": false, "text": "26" },{ "correct": false, "text": "920" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "509 - -738", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "2109" },{ "correct": false, "text": "385" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1246" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1247" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "876 / -559", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.5670840787119857" },{ "correct": false, "text": "248.43291592128801" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.5670840787119857" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-251.56708407871199" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "937 - 156", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1282" },{ "correct": false, "text": "280" },{ "correct": true, "text": "781" },{ "correct": false, "text": "780" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-271 + -942", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1214" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-775" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1651" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1213" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "915 - -397", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1311" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1369" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1312" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1255" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "411 + 662", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1073" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1072" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1433" },{ "correct": false, "text": "713" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "18 * 52", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "515" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1357" },{ "correct": true, "text": "936" },{ "correct": false, "text": "935" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-887 + -915", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1803" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1236" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2368" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1802" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "796 + 858", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1654" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1101" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2207" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1653" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-559 + -896", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1617" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1293" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1455" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1456" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-337 - -580", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-203" },{ "correct": false, "text": "242" },{ "correct": false, "text": "689" },{ "correct": true, "text": "243" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "853 / 912", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-112.06469298245614" },{ "correct": false, "text": "113.93530701754386" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.9353070175438597" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.0646929824561403" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "359 + -865", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "86" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-507" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1098" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-506" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-50 + 420", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "599" },{ "correct": true, "text": "370" },{ "correct": false, "text": "369" },{ "correct": false, "text": "141" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "450 - -181", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "630" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-169" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1431" },{ "correct": true, "text": "631" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-270 + -850", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-131" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1120" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2109" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1121" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "570 + 173", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "742" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1300" },{ "correct": true, "text": "743" },{ "correct": false, "text": "186" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "753 - 579", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1123" },{ "correct": true, "text": "174" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-775" },{ "correct": false, "text": "173" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-124 / 644", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-828.1925465838509" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.19254658385093168" },{ "correct": false, "text": "827.8074534161491" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.1925465838509317" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "112 - 562", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "392" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-450" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1292" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-451" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "136 * 848", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "115328" },{ "correct": false, "text": "115575" },{ "correct": false, "text": "115327" },{ "correct": false, "text": "115081" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-922 - 303", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1226" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1225" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1330" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1120" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-928 * -504", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "468695" },{ "correct": false, "text": "467711" },{ "correct": false, "text": "466729" },{ "correct": true, "text": "467712" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "171 + -659", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "324" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-489" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-488" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1300" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "270 / -49", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-592.5102040816327" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-5.510204081632653" },{ "correct": false, "text": "581.4897959183673" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-6.510204081632653" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "1000 / -833", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "814.7995198079232" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-817.2004801920768" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.2004801920768307" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.2004801920768307" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-848 + -25", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-430" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-873" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-874" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1316" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "883 * 715", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "631344" },{ "correct": false, "text": "630946" },{ "correct": true, "text": "631345" },{ "correct": false, "text": "631744" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-244 + 376", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "131" },{ "correct": false, "text": "166" },{ "correct": false, "text": "98" },{ "correct": true, "text": "132" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-545 + 75", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1420" },{ "correct": false, "text": "480" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-471" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-470" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "866 + 736", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1406" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1602" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1601" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1798" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "709 + 324", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1032" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1092" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1033" },{ "correct": false, "text": "974" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "462 - -809", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1759" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1271" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1270" },{ "correct": false, "text": "783" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-505 * 487", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-245936" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-246115" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-245755" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-245935" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-966 + -547", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1596" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1514" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1430" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1513" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-463 / 462", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.0021645021645025" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-381.0021645021645" },{ "correct": false, "text": "378.9978354978355" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.0021645021645023" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "293 + -314", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "302" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-21" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-22" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-344" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "813 + 750", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1512" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1563" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1614" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1562" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "49 + -666", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-888" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-618" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-617" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-346" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "462 + 837", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1299" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1298" },{ "correct": false, "text": "790" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1808" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "489 / -55", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-21.89090909090909" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-8.89090909090909" },{ "correct": false, "text": "4.109090909090909" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-9.89090909090909" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-814 - 892", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1706" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1669" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1707" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1743" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "958 / 962", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.9958419958419958" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.004158004158004158" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-310.004158004158" },{ "correct": false, "text": "311.995841995842" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "878 / -51", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-18.215686274509803" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-451.2156862745098" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-17.215686274509803" },{ "correct": false, "text": "416.7843137254902" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "188 * -48", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-8776" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-9024" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-9025" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-9272" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-731 / -217", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "3.3686635944700463" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-223.63133640552996" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2.3686635944700463" },{ "correct": false, "text": "230.36866359447004" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "403 / -955", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-829.4219895287958" },{ "correct": false, "text": "828.5780104712042" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.42198952879581153" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.4219895287958115" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-882 / -115", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-306.3304347826087" },{ "correct": false, "text": "321.6695652173913" },{ "correct": false, "text": "6.6695652173913045" },{ "correct": true, "text": "7.6695652173913045" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-788 / 646", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.219814241486068" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.2198142414860682" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-232.21981424148606" },{ "correct": false, "text": "229.78018575851394" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "94 + -34", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-560" },{ "correct": false, "text": "680" },{ "correct": false, "text": "59" },{ "correct": true, "text": "60" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-748 * 164", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-122673" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-122672" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-121692" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-123652" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "399 + -60", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1233" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-555" },{ "correct": true, "text": "339" },{ "correct": false, "text": "338" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "911 + 296", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1206" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1207" },{ "correct": false, "text": "852" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1562" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "112 / -489", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.22903885480572597" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.229038854805726" },{ "correct": false, "text": "55.77096114519427" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-56.22903885480573" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "336 / 149", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-947.744966442953" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1.2550335570469797" },{ "correct": true, "text": "2.2550335570469797" },{ "correct": false, "text": "952.255033557047" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "591 + -534", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "57" },{ "correct": false, "text": "515" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-401" },{ "correct": false, "text": "56" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-359 / 332", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "454.9186746987952" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-457.0813253012048" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.0813253012048192" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.081325301204819" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "323 / 514", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "581.6284046692607" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.6284046692607004" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.3715953307392996" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-580.3715953307393" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "1000 - -596", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1596" },{ "correct": false, "text": "854" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1595" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2338" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-983 + -930", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-971" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1914" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1913" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2855" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-506 * 125", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-63250" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-63811" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-62689" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-63251" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-653 * 434", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-283577" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-283402" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-283403" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-283227" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-785 + 233", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-509" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-595" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-553" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-552" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "804 / -686", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "408.8279883381924" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.1720116618075802" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-411.1720116618076" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.17201166180758" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-892 - -117", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-775" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1490" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-60" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-776" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "18 - -433", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-311" },{ "correct": true, "text": "451" },{ "correct": false, "text": "450" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1213" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "53 * 472", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "25183" },{ "correct": false, "text": "24849" },{ "correct": false, "text": "25015" },{ "correct": true, "text": "25016" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "532 + -141", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "391" },{ "correct": false, "text": "390" },{ "correct": false, "text": "736" },{ "correct": false, "text": "46" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "818 * 354", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "289572" },{ "correct": false, "text": "289571" },{ "correct": false, "text": "289294" },{ "correct": false, "text": "289850" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-97 * 784", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-75592" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-76049" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-76504" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-76048" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "758 * -11", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-8338" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-8339" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-8089" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-8587" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-891 - -31", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-861" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-86" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-860" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1634" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-334 + -817", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-228" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2074" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1151" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1152" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-477 / 113", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-247.2212389380531" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-4.221238938053097" },{ "correct": false, "text": "238.7787610619469" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-5.221238938053097" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-137 * -104", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "14109" },{ "correct": false, "text": "14387" },{ "correct": false, "text": "14247" },{ "correct": true, "text": "14248" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-591 + 18", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-574" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-339" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-807" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-573" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-504 / 844", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.5971563981042654" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.5971563981042654" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-155.59715639810426" },{ "correct": false, "text": "154.40284360189574" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-369 - -165", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-205" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-204" },{ "correct": false, "text": "108" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-516" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-119 / -394", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-587.6979695431472" },{ "correct": false, "text": "588.3020304568528" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.3020304568527919" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.6979695431472082" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "940 * 573", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "538333" },{ "correct": true, "text": "538620" },{ "correct": false, "text": "538907" },{ "correct": false, "text": "538619" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "107 * 745", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "80070" },{ "correct": true, "text": "79715" },{ "correct": false, "text": "79714" },{ "correct": false, "text": "79360" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-744 * 142", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-104679" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-105649" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-105648" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-106617" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-378 * 621", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-235704" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-233772" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-234738" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-234739" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "191 * -796", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-151433" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-152036" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-152037" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-152639" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-781 - -569", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-717" },{ "correct": false, "text": "293" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-212" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-213" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-601 - 999", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1539" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1600" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1661" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1601" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "699 + -638", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "16" },{ "correct": false, "text": "60" },{ "correct": false, "text": "106" },{ "correct": true, "text": "61" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-855 - 256", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1111" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-336" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1112" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1886" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-638 * -728", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "464463" },{ "correct": false, "text": "464158" },{ "correct": false, "text": "464770" },{ "correct": true, "text": "464464" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "966 - 98", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "867" },{ "correct": true, "text": "868" },{ "correct": false, "text": "631" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1105" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "828 * 261", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "215822" },{ "correct": false, "text": "216394" },{ "correct": false, "text": "216107" },{ "correct": true, "text": "216108" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-256 - 575", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-831" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-832" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-488" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1174" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "374 - 148", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "226" },{ "correct": false, "text": "225" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-186" },{ "correct": false, "text": "638" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-477 - 817", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-992" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1596" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1295" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1294" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-60 + -373", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-334" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-434" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-532" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-433" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "99 + -658", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-560" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-559" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-640" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-478" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-147 / -81", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1.8148148148148149" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-657.1851851851852" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.8148148148148149" },{ "correct": false, "text": "660.8148148148148" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "819 * 388", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "317772" },{ "correct": false, "text": "317771" },{ "correct": false, "text": "317682" },{ "correct": false, "text": "317862" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "218 / 738", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-531.7046070460705" },{ "correct": false, "text": "532.2953929539295" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.7046070460704608" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.2953929539295393" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-110 / -581", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.18932874354561102" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.810671256454389" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-835.8106712564544" },{ "correct": false, "text": "836.1893287435456" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-529 - -340", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-190" },{ "correct": false, "text": "460" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-189" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-838" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "427 + 59", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "485" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-472" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1444" },{ "correct": true, "text": "486" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "751 / 470", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "450.5978723404255" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.597872340425532" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-447.4021276595745" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.597872340425532" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-792 / 440", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "856.2" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.8" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.8" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-859.8" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-809 * -176", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "142384" },{ "correct": false, "text": "142987" },{ "correct": false, "text": "141781" },{ "correct": false, "text": "142383" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "302 / 255", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1.184313725490196" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-500.8156862745098" },{ "correct": false, "text": "503.1843137254902" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.1843137254901961" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "961 + 89", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1049" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1818" },{ "correct": false, "text": "282" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1050" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "196 / -758", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.25857519788918204" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.258575197889182" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-785.2585751978892" },{ "correct": false, "text": "784.7414248021108" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "798 * -701", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-559486" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-559398" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-559399" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-559310" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "155 - 391", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "97" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-237" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-236" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-569" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "282 - -762", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1044" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1043" },{ "correct": false, "text": "67" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2021" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-604 - 609", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1214" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-833" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1593" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1213" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "584 + -315", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1013" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-475" },{ "correct": true, "text": "269" },{ "correct": false, "text": "268" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-145 - 619", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-764" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-765" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-297" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1231" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-951 - -766", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "540" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-910" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-186" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-185" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "820 - -542", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1362" },{ "correct": false, "text": "390" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2334" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1361" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-139 + -947", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1087" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1139" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1086" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1033" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "300 - -621", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "921" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1309" },{ "correct": false, "text": "533" },{ "correct": false, "text": "920" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "881 - 307", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "574" },{ "correct": false, "text": "198" },{ "correct": false, "text": "950" },{ "correct": false, "text": "573" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "610 * -826", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-503861" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-503355" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-503860" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-504365" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-249 / 253", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.9841897233201582" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-306.9841897233202" },{ "correct": false, "text": "305.0158102766798" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.9841897233201581" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "779 + 226", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1502" },{ "correct": false, "text": "508" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1005" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1004" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-856 + -422", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1279" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1201" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1355" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1278" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "169 * 923", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "155868" },{ "correct": true, "text": "155987" },{ "correct": false, "text": "156106" },{ "correct": false, "text": "155986" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-585 / 763", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.7667103538663171" },{ "correct": false, "text": "886.2332896461337" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-887.7667103538663" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.7667103538663171" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "810 + 553", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1362" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1231" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1363" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1495" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "493 - -643", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1232" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1040" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1136" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1135" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-905 + -289", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-207" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1194" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2181" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1195" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-8 * 399", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-3966" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2418" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-3193" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-3192" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-38 / 227", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "20.83259911894273" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.1674008810572687" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.16740088105726872" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-21.16740088105727" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "353 * -175", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-61776" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-62033" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-61517" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-61775" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-307 / -357", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "739.859943977591" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.8599439775910365" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-738.140056022409" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.14005602240896353" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "797 * 681", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "542757" },{ "correct": false, "text": "542756" },{ "correct": false, "text": "542034" },{ "correct": false, "text": "543480" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-527 - -362", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1134" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-165" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-166" },{ "correct": false, "text": "804" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "931 / -593", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-739.5699831365936" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.569983136593592" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.569983136593592" },{ "correct": false, "text": "736.4300168634064" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-275 + -662", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-938" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1165" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-709" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-937" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "25 * -966", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-24151" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-24779" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-24150" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-23521" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-858 - 802", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1660" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2067" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1661" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1253" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "930 + -568", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1291" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-567" },{ "correct": true, "text": "362" },{ "correct": false, "text": "361" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "366 / -625", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.5856" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-539.5856" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.5856" },{ "correct": false, "text": "538.4144" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-599 - 697", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1296" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-908" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1684" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1297" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-146 / -279", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.5232974910394266" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.4767025089605734" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-813.4767025089606" },{ "correct": false, "text": "814.5232974910394" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "821 + -251", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "39" },{ "correct": false, "text": "569" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1101" },{ "correct": true, "text": "570" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-836 / -200", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "863.18" },{ "correct": false, "text": "3.1799999999999997" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-854.82" },{ "correct": true, "text": "4.18" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-94 / -789", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.11913814955640051" },{ "correct": false, "text": "446.1191381495564" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-445.8808618504436" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.8808618504435994" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-120 + -918", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-323" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1753" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1038" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1039" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-174 / 377", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "750.5384615384615" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-751.4615384615385" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.4615384615384617" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.46153846153846156" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-871 + 631", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-240" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-241" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-416" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-64" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "708 / -860", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-259.8232558139535" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.8232558139534882" },{ "correct": false, "text": "258.1767441860465" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.8232558139534883" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-209 * -905", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "189144" },{ "correct": true, "text": "189145" },{ "correct": false, "text": "189265" },{ "correct": false, "text": "189025" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-469 - 373", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-842" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-366" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-843" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1318" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "23 / -977", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "60.97645854657114" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.0235414534288638" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-61.02354145342886" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.02354145342886387" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-169 + 651", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "482" },{ "correct": false, "text": "68" },{ "correct": false, "text": "896" },{ "correct": false, "text": "481" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-650 + -516", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1166" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-987" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1345" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1167" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-882 + -314", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1197" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-215" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2177" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1196" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-98 * 298", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-28533" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-29875" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-29205" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-29204" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "257 / -663", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.38763197586727" },{ "correct": false, "text": "218.61236802413273" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.38763197586727" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-219.38763197586727" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "57 * -222", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-12654" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-12655" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-12381" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-12927" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-337 - 774", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1111" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1112" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2101" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-121" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "665 - 353", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "311" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-116" },{ "correct": true, "text": "312" },{ "correct": false, "text": "740" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-445 * 530", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-236767" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-235850" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-234933" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-235851" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "669 - -931", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1284" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1916" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1600" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1599" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "422 + 417", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1040" },{ "correct": false, "text": "638" },{ "correct": false, "text": "838" },{ "correct": true, "text": "839" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "465 - 174", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "290" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1227" },{ "correct": true, "text": "291" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-645" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-988 * 209", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-206493" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-205698" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-207286" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-206492" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "978 - 924", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "54" },{ "correct": false, "text": "53" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-330" },{ "correct": false, "text": "438" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "459 + -960", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-502" },{ "correct": false, "text": "378" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1380" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-501" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "174 - -694", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "478" },{ "correct": true, "text": "868" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1258" },{ "correct": false, "text": "867" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "549 - 807", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-448" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-68" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-259" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-258" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "314 / 800", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.6074999999999999" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-845.6075" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.3925" },{ "correct": false, "text": "846.3925" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-908 / -243", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-243.2633744855967" },{ "correct": false, "text": "250.7366255144033" },{ "correct": true, "text": "3.736625514403292" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2.736625514403292" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "224 - -774", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1660" },{ "correct": true, "text": "998" },{ "correct": false, "text": "336" },{ "correct": false, "text": "997" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "405 + 989", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "2085" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1393" },{ "correct": false, "text": "703" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1394" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-862 + -992", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1855" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2145" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1563" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1854" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-488 + -449", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1278" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-596" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-937" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-938" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "378 - 209", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-78" },{ "correct": false, "text": "416" },{ "correct": true, "text": "169" },{ "correct": false, "text": "168" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-520 * -529", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "275883" },{ "correct": false, "text": "274277" },{ "correct": true, "text": "275080" },{ "correct": false, "text": "275079" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "909 - 492", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "417" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1131" },{ "correct": false, "text": "416" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-297" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-968 - -889", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "310" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-79" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-80" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-468" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "785 - 421", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-130" },{ "correct": false, "text": "363" },{ "correct": true, "text": "364" },{ "correct": false, "text": "858" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "818 + 773", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "2183" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1591" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1590" },{ "correct": false, "text": "999" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "784 * 640", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "501759" },{ "correct": false, "text": "502541" },{ "correct": false, "text": "500979" },{ "correct": true, "text": "501760" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-501 - 503", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1415" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-593" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1004" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1005" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-884 * -237", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "209507" },{ "correct": true, "text": "209508" },{ "correct": false, "text": "210453" },{ "correct": false, "text": "208563" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "364 / 878", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.5854214123006833" },{ "correct": false, "text": "595.4145785876993" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.4145785876993166" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-594.5854214123007" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "68 / 50", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1.36" },{ "correct": false, "text": "374.36" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-371.64" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.3600000000000001" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "554 * -903", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-499899" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-500263" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-500262" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-500625" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-771 + 309", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1023" },{ "correct": false, "text": "99" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-463" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-462" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-688 - -490", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "118" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-199" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-514" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-198" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-969 * -635", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "614898" },{ "correct": false, "text": "615732" },{ "correct": false, "text": "615314" },{ "correct": true, "text": "615315" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "498 / -565", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.88141592920354" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.8814159292035398" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-699.8814159292035" },{ "correct": false, "text": "698.1185840707965" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "62 * -988", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-62144" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-61257" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-61256" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-60368" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-137 + -450", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-502" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-588" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-672" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-587" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "37 / -677", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-591.0546528803545" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.05465288035450517" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.0546528803545052" },{ "correct": false, "text": "590.9453471196455" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "609 - -928", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1536" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1537" },{ "correct": false, "text": "808" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2266" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-580 / 981", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-969.5912334352702" },{ "correct": false, "text": "968.4087665647298" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.5912334352701325" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.5912334352701325" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-805 * 453", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-364577" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-364753" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-364665" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-364666" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "488 * -164", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-79887" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-80177" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-80032" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-80033" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "614 * 62", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "38067" },{ "correct": false, "text": "38032" },{ "correct": true, "text": "38068" },{ "correct": false, "text": "38104" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "819 / 853", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.9601406799531067" },{ "correct": false, "text": "270.9601406799531" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-269.0398593200469" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.0398593200468933" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "794 * 493", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "391441" },{ "correct": false, "text": "390606" },{ "correct": false, "text": "392278" },{ "correct": true, "text": "391442" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-493 + 363", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-131" },{ "correct": false, "text": "798" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-130" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1058" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-488 - -251", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1214" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-237" },{ "correct": false, "text": "740" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-238" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-629 + 161", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-73" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-863" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-468" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-469" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-631 + -931", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-2333" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1563" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-791" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1562" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-607 + -704", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1222" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1311" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1312" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1400" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "117 * -147", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-17057" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-17199" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-17200" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-17341" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-661 * 671", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-443532" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-443531" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-443365" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-443697" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "508 - -700", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "909" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1207" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1208" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1507" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-551 + -272", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-666" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-823" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-824" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-980" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "561 + 861", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1422" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1136" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1708" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1421" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-914 - -483", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-850" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-12" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-432" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-431" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-761 - 522", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1284" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1630" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-936" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1283" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-844 - 673", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1269" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1765" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1517" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1518" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "824 * -210", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-173041" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-172208" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-173872" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-173040" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-394 * -618", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "242513" },{ "correct": false, "text": "244471" },{ "correct": false, "text": "243491" },{ "correct": true, "text": "243492" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-190 * -797", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "152268" },{ "correct": false, "text": "151429" },{ "correct": false, "text": "150592" },{ "correct": true, "text": "151430" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "919 / 1", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "918" },{ "correct": false, "text": "866" },{ "correct": true, "text": "919" },{ "correct": false, "text": "972" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-718 / 384", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.869791666666667" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.8697916666666667" },{ "correct": false, "text": "829.1302083333334" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-832.8697916666666" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "922 * 583", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "537112" },{ "correct": true, "text": "537526" },{ "correct": false, "text": "537940" },{ "correct": false, "text": "537525" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-39 / 399", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.0977443609022557" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-54.097744360902254" },{ "correct": false, "text": "53.902255639097746" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.09774436090225563" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "680 + 174", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "974" },{ "correct": false, "text": "853" },{ "correct": false, "text": "734" },{ "correct": true, "text": "854" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "664 - 211", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "453" },{ "correct": false, "text": "935" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-29" },{ "correct": false, "text": "452" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "937 * -28", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-25826" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-26236" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-26646" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-26237" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "495 / 773", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "531.6403622250971" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-530.3596377749029" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.6403622250970246" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.35963777490297544" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "316 * -517", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-163372" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-163373" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-162421" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-164323" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-969 / -126", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "7.690476190476191" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-727.3095238095239" },{ "correct": false, "text": "742.6904761904761" },{ "correct": false, "text": "6.690476190476191" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-820 + -425", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1246" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-345" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1245" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2145" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-220 * 436", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-95440" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-95921" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-95920" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-96400" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "23 * -940", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-21621" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-21620" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-21630" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-21610" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "116 * 696", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "81035" },{ "correct": false, "text": "80735" },{ "correct": false, "text": "80437" },{ "correct": true, "text": "80736" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "168 * 344", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "57791" },{ "correct": true, "text": "57792" },{ "correct": false, "text": "58475" },{ "correct": false, "text": "57109" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "222 - 578", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-41" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-671" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-357" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-356" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-659 + -14", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1100" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-246" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-673" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-674" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "943 * 177", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "166403" },{ "correct": false, "text": "167419" },{ "correct": true, "text": "166911" },{ "correct": false, "text": "166910" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "876 + -255", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "620" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-94" },{ "correct": true, "text": "621" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1336" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "871 * 190", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "165575" },{ "correct": true, "text": "165490" },{ "correct": false, "text": "165405" },{ "correct": false, "text": "165489" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "443 * -140", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-61042" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-62020" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-62021" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-62998" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-143 + -358", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-501" },{ "correct": false, "text": "238" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1240" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-502" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "487 - 653", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-166" },{ "correct": false, "text": "430" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-762" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-167" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-107 * 447", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-47829" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-48815" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-46843" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-47830" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "923 + 6", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "419" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1439" },{ "correct": false, "text": "928" },{ "correct": true, "text": "929" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-186 + -508", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-694" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-695" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-791" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-597" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "196 + -539", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-344" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-685" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-343" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-918 / -724", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1.2679558011049723" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-25.73204419889503" },{ "correct": false, "text": "28.26795580110497" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.2679558011049723" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "751 / -569", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "526.6801405975395" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.3198594024604569" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.319859402460457" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-529.3198594024605" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-373 * -491", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "183142" },{ "correct": true, "text": "183143" },{ "correct": false, "text": "183511" },{ "correct": false, "text": "182775" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "971 + 704", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1675" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1384" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1966" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1674" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "512 - -733", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1244" },{ "correct": false, "text": "439" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2051" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1245" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-779 * 753", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-586537" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-586587" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-586588" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-586637" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "505 - -71", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "576" },{ "correct": false, "text": "575" },{ "correct": false, "text": "651" },{ "correct": false, "text": "501" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "375 / 575", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "794.6521739130435" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.34782608695652173" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.6521739130434783" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-793.3478260869565" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-567 + 885", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "318" },{ "correct": false, "text": "58" },{ "correct": false, "text": "317" },{ "correct": false, "text": "578" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-507 - 101", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-609" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-608" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1502" },{ "correct": false, "text": "286" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-175 - -286", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "496" },{ "correct": true, "text": "111" },{ "correct": false, "text": "110" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-274" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-586 / -909", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.35533553355335534" },{ "correct": false, "text": "988.6446644664467" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-987.3553355335533" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.6446644664466447" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "616 * 138", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "85008" },{ "correct": false, "text": "85007" },{ "correct": false, "text": "84104" },{ "correct": false, "text": "85912" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "664 * 682", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "452041" },{ "correct": false, "text": "452847" },{ "correct": true, "text": "452848" },{ "correct": false, "text": "453655" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "894 / 674", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-478.67359050445106" },{ "correct": false, "text": "481.32640949554894" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.32640949554896137" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.3264094955489614" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-71 - -173", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-858" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1062" },{ "correct": false, "text": "101" },{ "correct": true, "text": "102" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-380 - 570", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-950" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-951" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1631" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-269" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "118 * -639", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-75402" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-76106" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-75403" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-74698" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-388 - -682", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "294" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-662" },{ "correct": false, "text": "293" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1250" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "297 + 325", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1395" },{ "correct": false, "text": "621" },{ "correct": true, "text": "622" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-151" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "344 - 716", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-372" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1150" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-373" },{ "correct": false, "text": "406" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-174 / 106", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-339.64150943396226" },{ "correct": false, "text": "336.35849056603774" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.6415094339622645" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.6415094339622642" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "988 * 115", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "113748" },{ "correct": false, "text": "113492" },{ "correct": false, "text": "113619" },{ "correct": true, "text": "113620" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-566 / -270", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-52.903703703703705" },{ "correct": false, "text": "57.096296296296295" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1.096296296296296" },{ "correct": true, "text": "2.096296296296296" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "484 + 668", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1151" },{ "correct": false, "text": "176" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2128" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1152" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-973 * -914", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "889745" },{ "correct": false, "text": "889321" },{ "correct": true, "text": "889322" },{ "correct": false, "text": "888899" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "148 - -669", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "816" },{ "correct": false, "text": "672" },{ "correct": true, "text": "817" },{ "correct": false, "text": "962" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-215 * 845", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-181897" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-181675" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-181453" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-181676" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-474 * -837", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "396737" },{ "correct": true, "text": "396738" },{ "correct": false, "text": "397067" },{ "correct": false, "text": "396409" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "149 * -799", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-120024" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-119051" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-118078" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-119052" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-662 - 226", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1368" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-888" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-408" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-889" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "770 - -924", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1693" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1288" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2100" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1694" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-483 - -607", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "123" },{ "correct": true, "text": "124" },{ "correct": false, "text": "383" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-135" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "435 - -501", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "935" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1643" },{ "correct": false, "text": "229" },{ "correct": true, "text": "936" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-609 * 291", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-176439" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-177999" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-177220" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-177219" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "487 + -823", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-336" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-337" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1048" },{ "correct": false, "text": "376" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-984 * -634", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "623855" },{ "correct": false, "text": "624513" },{ "correct": false, "text": "623199" },{ "correct": true, "text": "623856" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "376 * 482", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "181572" },{ "correct": false, "text": "181231" },{ "correct": true, "text": "181232" },{ "correct": false, "text": "180892" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-796 + -336", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1481" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1133" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-783" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1132" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "289 / -328", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.8810975609756098" },{ "correct": false, "text": "118.1189024390244" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.8810975609756098" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-119.8810975609756" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-45 + 879", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1518" },{ "correct": false, "text": "833" },{ "correct": true, "text": "834" },{ "correct": false, "text": "150" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-917 + 389", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-529" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-528" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-80" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-976" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "692 - -805", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1497" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1428" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1496" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1566" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-766 - -747", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "37" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-20" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-75" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-19" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-536 / 60", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-9.933333333333334" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-8.933333333333334" },{ "correct": false, "text": "697.0666666666667" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-714.9333333333333" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-750 * -439", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "329250" },{ "correct": false, "text": "329992" },{ "correct": false, "text": "329249" },{ "correct": false, "text": "328508" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-187 * 592", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-110704" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-110183" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-110705" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-111225" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-413 - -41", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-196" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-373" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-548" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-372" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "45 * -830", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-37559" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-37141" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-37351" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-37350" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "178 - -150", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1152" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-496" },{ "correct": true, "text": "328" },{ "correct": false, "text": "327" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-655 + 274", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-382" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-51" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-381" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-711" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-390 + -132", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-666" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-522" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-523" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-378" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "33 / 202", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-767.8366336633663" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.16336633663366337" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.8366336633663366" },{ "correct": false, "text": "768.1633663366337" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "105 / 960", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.890625" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.109375" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-334.890625" },{ "correct": false, "text": "335.109375" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-313 * -866", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "271058" },{ "correct": false, "text": "271057" },{ "correct": false, "text": "271317" },{ "correct": false, "text": "270799" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "582 + 486", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1067" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1602" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1068" },{ "correct": false, "text": "534" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-657 * -561", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "368658" },{ "correct": false, "text": "368576" },{ "correct": false, "text": "368496" },{ "correct": true, "text": "368577" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "621 * -787", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-488727" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-488091" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-488728" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-489363" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-664 * 763", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-507045" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-506632" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-506219" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-506633" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "214 * 324", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "68916" },{ "correct": false, "text": "69335" },{ "correct": true, "text": "69336" },{ "correct": false, "text": "69756" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "363 * 655", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "238626" },{ "correct": true, "text": "237765" },{ "correct": false, "text": "236904" },{ "correct": false, "text": "237764" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "857 * -243", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-209128" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-208251" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-207374" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-208252" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "456 - 432", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "24" },{ "correct": false, "text": "351" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-303" },{ "correct": false, "text": "23" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "861 - 470", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-37" },{ "correct": false, "text": "390" },{ "correct": true, "text": "391" },{ "correct": false, "text": "819" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-578 + -876", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-899" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1455" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2009" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1454" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-15 + -893", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-909" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-974" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-842" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-908" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "131 - 849", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1085" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-719" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-718" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-351" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "818 - 842", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-24" },{ "correct": false, "text": "572" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-620" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-25" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "657 - 918", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-261" },{ "correct": false, "text": "505" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-262" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1027" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "809 - 588", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "220" },{ "correct": true, "text": "221" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-570" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1012" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "564 - -786", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1350" },{ "correct": false, "text": "459" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1349" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2241" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-503 - 452", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-955" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-404" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1506" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-956" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "669 / -797", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-64.83939774153075" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.8393977415307403" },{ "correct": false, "text": "63.16060225846926" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.8393977415307403" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "351 + 27", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "377" },{ "correct": false, "text": "817" },{ "correct": true, "text": "378" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-61" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "106 - 196", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-90" },{ "correct": false, "text": "471" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-91" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-651" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-974 - 328", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-2119" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1303" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-485" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1302" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-875 / -109", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-704.9724770642201" },{ "correct": false, "text": "721.0275229357799" },{ "correct": true, "text": "8.027522935779816" },{ "correct": false, "text": "7.027522935779816" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "732 + -91", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "640" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-158" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1440" },{ "correct": true, "text": "641" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-873 / 652", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.338957055214724" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-799.3389570552147" },{ "correct": false, "text": "796.6610429447853" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.3389570552147239" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "392 / 890", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.4404494382022472" },{ "correct": false, "text": "747.4404494382022" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-746.5595505617978" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.5595505617977528" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-62 - -357", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1005" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-415" },{ "correct": true, "text": "295" },{ "correct": false, "text": "294" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-43 * -177", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "6970" },{ "correct": true, "text": "7611" },{ "correct": false, "text": "7610" },{ "correct": false, "text": "8252" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-491 * -494", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "242554" },{ "correct": false, "text": "243268" },{ "correct": false, "text": "242553" },{ "correct": false, "text": "241840" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-751 * 423", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-318154" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-317673" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-317192" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-317674" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-166 / -250", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.664" },{ "correct": false, "text": "887.664" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-886.336" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.33599999999999997" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-165 * -135", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "22975" },{ "correct": false, "text": "21575" },{ "correct": false, "text": "22274" },{ "correct": true, "text": "22275" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "777 + 609", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1259" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1385" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1513" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1386" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "815 + -338", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "993" },{ "correct": true, "text": "477" },{ "correct": false, "text": "476" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-39" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-222 / 250", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.888" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-293.888" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.888" },{ "correct": false, "text": "292.112" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-857 + 968", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "111" },{ "correct": false, "text": "391" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-169" },{ "correct": false, "text": "110" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "817 - 186", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "133" },{ "correct": false, "text": "630" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1129" },{ "correct": true, "text": "631" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "906 / 835", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-871.9149700598803" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.0850299401197605" },{ "correct": false, "text": "874.0850299401197" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.0850299401197605" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "527 + 588", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1115" },{ "correct": false, "text": "157" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2073" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1114" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "476 + 666", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1142" },{ "correct": false, "text": "920" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1364" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1141" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "715 - -86", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "801" },{ "correct": false, "text": "483" },{ "correct": false, "text": "800" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1119" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-993 - 776", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-2118" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1770" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1420" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1769" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-309 + -482", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-792" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-791" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-317" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1265" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "453 * 310", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "140271" },{ "correct": false, "text": "140589" },{ "correct": false, "text": "140429" },{ "correct": true, "text": "140430" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-933 + -477", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-2113" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1411" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-707" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1410" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-971 * 72", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-69419" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-69913" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-69912" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-70405" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-940 + -109", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1050" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-378" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1720" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1049" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-667 / -828", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "421.80555555555554" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.8055555555555556" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.19444444444444442" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-420.19444444444446" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "469 * -73", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-34237" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-34750" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-34238" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-33724" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "325 - -909", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1723" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1234" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1233" },{ "correct": false, "text": "745" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "382 / 955", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "61.4" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.6" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.4" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-60.6" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-63 * 275", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-17162" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-17488" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-17326" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-17325" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-499 - -288", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-212" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-633" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-211" },{ "correct": false, "text": "211" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "464 / 259", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "689.7915057915058" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.7915057915057915" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-686.2084942084942" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.7915057915057915" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-76 * -729", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "55404" },{ "correct": false, "text": "55403" },{ "correct": false, "text": "54861" },{ "correct": false, "text": "55947" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-527 + -620", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1148" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1336" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1147" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-958" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-888 - -931", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "707" },{ "correct": false, "text": "42" },{ "correct": true, "text": "43" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-621" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "345 + 142", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-331" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1305" },{ "correct": true, "text": "487" },{ "correct": false, "text": "486" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-388 / 629", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-685.6168521462639" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.6168521462639109" },{ "correct": false, "text": "684.3831478537361" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.616852146263911" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-739 * -900", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "664714" },{ "correct": true, "text": "665100" },{ "correct": false, "text": "665099" },{ "correct": false, "text": "665486" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-995 - 695", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1691" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2276" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1104" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1690" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "275 * 275", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "75624" },{ "correct": false, "text": "75555" },{ "correct": true, "text": "75625" },{ "correct": false, "text": "75695" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "535 + 590", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "2106" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1124" },{ "correct": false, "text": "144" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1125" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "223 - 65", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "158" },{ "correct": false, "text": "821" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-505" },{ "correct": false, "text": "157" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "345 + -281", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-304" },{ "correct": false, "text": "63" },{ "correct": false, "text": "432" },{ "correct": true, "text": "64" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-973 * -769", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "748236" },{ "correct": false, "text": "747906" },{ "correct": false, "text": "748568" },{ "correct": true, "text": "748237" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-803 / -405", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "500.9827160493827" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.9827160493827161" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.982716049382716" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-497.0172839506173" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-796 - 797", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1594" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-763" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2423" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1593" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "873 + -305", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "696" },{ "correct": false, "text": "567" },{ "correct": false, "text": "440" },{ "correct": true, "text": "568" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-910 - -188", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-723" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-634" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-810" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-722" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-471 + -445", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1580" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-916" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-252" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-917" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-239 / 224", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "542.9330357142857" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.0669642857142856" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.0669642857142858" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-545.0669642857143" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "739 + 790", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1529" },{ "correct": false, "text": "998" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2060" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1528" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-907 / -110", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "217.24545454545455" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-200.75454545454545" },{ "correct": true, "text": "8.245454545454546" },{ "correct": false, "text": "7.245454545454546" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-888 * -853", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "758334" },{ "correct": false, "text": "756594" },{ "correct": false, "text": "757463" },{ "correct": true, "text": "757464" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "783 - 687", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "96" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-37" },{ "correct": false, "text": "95" },{ "correct": false, "text": "229" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-929 / 314", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "151.04140127388536" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-2.9585987261146496" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-3.9585987261146496" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-156.95859872611464" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-134 - 593", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "219" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-727" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-728" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1673" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-657 / -462", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-697.577922077922" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.422077922077922" },{ "correct": false, "text": "700.422077922078" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.42207792207792205" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "138 / -238", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.5798319327731094" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-830.5798319327731" },{ "correct": false, "text": "829.4201680672269" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.5798319327731093" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "597 * 313", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "186004" },{ "correct": true, "text": "186861" },{ "correct": false, "text": "186860" },{ "correct": false, "text": "187718" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-653 * 130", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-84890" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-85771" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-84891" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-84009" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "826 / 449", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1.8396436525612472" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.8396436525612472" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-34.16035634743875" },{ "correct": false, "text": "37.83964365256125" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-167 - 863", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1030" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1031" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-669" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1391" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "322 - -440", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "761" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1519" },{ "correct": true, "text": "762" },{ "correct": false, "text": "5" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-123 - 930", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-72" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1053" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2034" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1054" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-743 / -541", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "0.37338262476894646" },{ "correct": false, "text": "352.37338262476896" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.3733826247689465" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-349.62661737523104" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "78 - -536", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "614" },{ "correct": false, "text": "613" },{ "correct": false, "text": "570" },{ "correct": false, "text": "658" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "783 - -932", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "2096" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1334" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1715" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1714" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-219 + 838", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-256" },{ "correct": true, "text": "619" },{ "correct": false, "text": "618" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1494" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-704 * 431", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-303580" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-303425" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-303268" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-303424" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "33 * -530", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-17491" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-17490" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-17926" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-17054" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "51 - -25", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "76" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-823" },{ "correct": false, "text": "75" },{ "correct": false, "text": "975" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-658 * 936", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-616882" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-615889" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-614894" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-615888" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "411 - -156", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "567" },{ "correct": false, "text": "608" },{ "correct": false, "text": "526" },{ "correct": false, "text": "566" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-400 + -686", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-742" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1430" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1087" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1086" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "793 * -229", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-181597" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-180655" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-181598" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-182539" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "536 - 690", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-155" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-341" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-154" },{ "correct": false, "text": "33" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-504 / -72", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "7" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-477" },{ "correct": false, "text": "6" },{ "correct": false, "text": "491" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-902 + -64", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1110" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-822" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-966" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-967" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-291 - -674", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "382" },{ "correct": false, "text": "544" },{ "correct": false, "text": "222" },{ "correct": true, "text": "383" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-198 * 342", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-67662" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-67770" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-67716" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-67717" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-578 + 971", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "393" },{ "correct": false, "text": "392" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-257" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1043" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-846 - -337", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "116" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-510" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-509" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1134" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "418 / 938", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-32.55437100213219" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.44562899786780386" },{ "correct": false, "text": "33.44562899786781" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.5543710021321961" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "249 * -189", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-47061" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-47077" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-47062" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-47045" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "519 + 785", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1303" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1304" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1895" },{ "correct": false, "text": "713" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-520 * 904", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-470081" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-470989" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-470080" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-469171" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "34 - 330", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "176" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-296" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-297" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-768" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "395 / -764", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.5170157068062827" },{ "correct": false, "text": "515.4829842931937" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.5170157068062826" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-516.5170157068063" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-226 * -13", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "2937" },{ "correct": true, "text": "2938" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2233" },{ "correct": false, "text": "3643" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-386 + 767", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "744" },{ "correct": false, "text": "380" },{ "correct": true, "text": "381" },{ "correct": false, "text": "18" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-441 + 946", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1073" },{ "correct": true, "text": "505" },{ "correct": false, "text": "504" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-63" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-981 - -182", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1174" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-799" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-800" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-424" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "786 - -957", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1742" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1743" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1448" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2038" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-791 * -253", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "200122" },{ "correct": false, "text": "199139" },{ "correct": false, "text": "201107" },{ "correct": true, "text": "200123" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "686 * 398", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "272780" },{ "correct": false, "text": "273027" },{ "correct": false, "text": "273276" },{ "correct": true, "text": "273028" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-460 + 751", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "179" },{ "correct": false, "text": "290" },{ "correct": false, "text": "403" },{ "correct": true, "text": "291" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "955 * 478", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "456490" },{ "correct": false, "text": "456549" },{ "correct": false, "text": "456489" },{ "correct": false, "text": "456431" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-629 - -589", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-41" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-40" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-989" },{ "correct": false, "text": "909" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-397 * -554", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "219591" },{ "correct": true, "text": "219938" },{ "correct": false, "text": "220285" },{ "correct": false, "text": "219937" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "298 / -11", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-27.09090909090909" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-28.09090909090909" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-293.09090909090907" },{ "correct": false, "text": "238.9090909090909" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "831 * -846", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-703026" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-703027" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-703632" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-702420" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "667 / 904", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.7378318584070797" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-352.2621681415929" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.26216814159292035" },{ "correct": false, "text": "353.7378318584071" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-685 * 296", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-202761" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-202760" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-203268" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-202252" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "84 * -1000", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-84037" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-83963" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-84000" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-84001" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-268 * 808", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-216545" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-216544" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-215988" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-217100" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-9 + 78", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "69" },{ "correct": false, "text": "68" },{ "correct": false, "text": "325" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-187" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-382 - -195", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "281" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-188" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-187" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-655" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-668 - -834", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-506" },{ "correct": true, "text": "166" },{ "correct": false, "text": "165" },{ "correct": false, "text": "838" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-852 + 52", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-800" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1460" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-140" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-801" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "143 + -317", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-174" },{ "correct": false, "text": "313" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-175" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-661" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-703 / -882", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.2029478458049887" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-597.2029478458049" },{ "correct": false, "text": "598.7970521541951" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.7970521541950113" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "909 - 566", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "342" },{ "correct": true, "text": "343" },{ "correct": false, "text": "719" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-33" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-932 / -918", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1.0152505446623095" },{ "correct": false, "text": "306.0152505446623" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-303.9847494553377" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.015250544662309462" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "98 / -235", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "15.582978723404254" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.41702127659574467" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.4170212765957446" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-16.417021276595744" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-749 + 331", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-811" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-419" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-25" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-418" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "859 / -644", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "938.666149068323" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-941.333850931677" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.3338509316770186" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.3338509316770186" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-919 * 495", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-454038" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-454905" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-454906" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-455772" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-371 - 147", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1112" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-519" },{ "correct": false, "text": "76" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-518" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "934 * 954", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "891036" },{ "correct": false, "text": "890393" },{ "correct": false, "text": "891035" },{ "correct": false, "text": "891679" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "170 / -858", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-797.1981351981352" },{ "correct": false, "text": "796.8018648018648" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.19813519813519814" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.1981351981351982" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-305 * 723", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-219559" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-220515" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-220516" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-221471" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "136 - -556", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "558" },{ "correct": false, "text": "691" },{ "correct": false, "text": "826" },{ "correct": true, "text": "692" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-581 / -797", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "857.7289836888331" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.27101631116687575" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-856.2710163111669" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.7289836888331243" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "873 * -88", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-76844" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-76825" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-76804" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-76824" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-253 / -327", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.7737003058103975" },{ "correct": false, "text": "150.7737003058104" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-149.2262996941896" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.2262996941896025" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "896 * -604", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-541663" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-541184" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-540705" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-541185" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "703 + 261", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "963" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1013" },{ "correct": true, "text": "964" },{ "correct": false, "text": "915" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-333 * -287", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "94895" },{ "correct": false, "text": "95570" },{ "correct": true, "text": "95571" },{ "correct": false, "text": "96247" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "650 / -274", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-2.372262773722628" },{ "correct": false, "text": "74.62773722627738" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-79.37226277372262" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-3.372262773722628" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-289 * -497", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "142818" },{ "correct": false, "text": "144448" },{ "correct": false, "text": "143632" },{ "correct": true, "text": "143633" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-25 * -897", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "21663" },{ "correct": false, "text": "23187" },{ "correct": false, "text": "22424" },{ "correct": true, "text": "22425" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "465 - -13", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "477" },{ "correct": true, "text": "478" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-234" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1190" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "948 * -229", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-216267" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-217092" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-217917" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-217093" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-4 / 871", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "156.99540757749713" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.0045924225028702" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.004592422502870264" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-157.00459242250287" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-885 + 171", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-59" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-714" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1369" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-715" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-265 - -174", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "589" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-771" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-92" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-91" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "288 * 166", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "47807" },{ "correct": false, "text": "47800" },{ "correct": false, "text": "47816" },{ "correct": true, "text": "47808" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "126 - 865", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-825" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-739" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-653" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-740" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "244 / 985", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.24771573604060915" },{ "correct": false, "text": "320.2477157360406" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-319.7522842639594" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.7522842639593909" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "412 * 810", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "334210" },{ "correct": true, "text": "333720" },{ "correct": false, "text": "333230" },{ "correct": false, "text": "333719" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-968 + -114", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1083" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1525" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1082" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-639" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-849 / 933", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.909967845659164" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-387.90996784565914" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.909967845659164" },{ "correct": false, "text": "386.09003215434086" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-664 + 708", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "44" },{ "correct": false, "text": "54" },{ "correct": false, "text": "34" },{ "correct": false, "text": "43" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "160 * 653", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "105322" },{ "correct": false, "text": "103638" },{ "correct": false, "text": "104479" },{ "correct": true, "text": "104480" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-784 / -125", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "966.272" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-953.728" },{ "correct": true, "text": "6.272" },{ "correct": false, "text": "5.272" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "630 - 869", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-240" },{ "correct": false, "text": "493" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-971" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-239" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "552 + -630", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-241" },{ "correct": false, "text": "85" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-78" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-79" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-674 / 828", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-654.8140096618357" },{ "correct": false, "text": "653.1859903381643" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.8140096618357487" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.8140096618357489" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "874 * -331", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-289295" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-289294" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-289132" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-289456" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "868 + 51", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "278" },{ "correct": true, "text": "919" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1560" },{ "correct": false, "text": "918" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "308 / 372", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.17204301075268813" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.8279569892473119" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-82.17204301075269" },{ "correct": false, "text": "83.82795698924731" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "382 + 912", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1294" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1051" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1293" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1537" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "17 / 128", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-675.8671875" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.1328125" },{ "correct": false, "text": "676.1328125" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.8671875" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "172 - -891", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1063" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1915" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1062" },{ "correct": false, "text": "211" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-795 / -837", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.9498207885304659" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.05017921146953408" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-765.0501792114695" },{ "correct": false, "text": "766.9498207885305" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-902 * 330", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-297661" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-297650" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-297660" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-297670" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "89 / 500", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.178" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-107.822" },{ "correct": false, "text": "108.178" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.8220000000000001" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "940 - 11", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1057" },{ "correct": true, "text": "929" },{ "correct": false, "text": "928" },{ "correct": false, "text": "801" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "276 + -849", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-364" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-573" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-574" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-782" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "502 * -619", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-310403" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-311073" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-310738" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-310739" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-339 * 293", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-99073" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-99328" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-99581" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-99327" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "554 * 896", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "496383" },{ "correct": false, "text": "495572" },{ "correct": true, "text": "496384" },{ "correct": false, "text": "497196" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "175 + 286", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "460" },{ "correct": false, "text": "264" },{ "correct": true, "text": "461" },{ "correct": false, "text": "658" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-391 - 285", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-843" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-676" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-509" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-677" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "110 * -969", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-106590" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-106591" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-106843" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-106337" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "550 - 490", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "475" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-355" },{ "correct": false, "text": "59" },{ "correct": true, "text": "60" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-498 * -829", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "412841" },{ "correct": true, "text": "412842" },{ "correct": false, "text": "411898" },{ "correct": false, "text": "413786" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "535 + 581", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1115" },{ "correct": false, "text": "439" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1793" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1116" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-446 / -977", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.5435005117707268" },{ "correct": false, "text": "130.45649948822927" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-129.54350051177073" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.4564994882292733" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "334 + -365", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "115" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-31" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-177" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-32" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-150 / 654", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "749.7706422018349" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-750.2293577981651" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.22935779816513763" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.2293577981651376" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "578 / 985", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.41319796954314725" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.5868020304568528" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-994.4131979695431" },{ "correct": false, "text": "995.5868020304569" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "643 * 284", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "182612" },{ "correct": false, "text": "181655" },{ "correct": false, "text": "182611" },{ "correct": false, "text": "183569" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "465 * 93", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "44124" },{ "correct": false, "text": "43244" },{ "correct": true, "text": "43245" },{ "correct": false, "text": "42366" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-238 - -488", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "249" },{ "correct": false, "text": "130" },{ "correct": false, "text": "370" },{ "correct": true, "text": "250" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "650 * 431", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "280149" },{ "correct": false, "text": "280574" },{ "correct": false, "text": "279726" },{ "correct": true, "text": "280150" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-864 + 400", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "132" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-464" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1060" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-465" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-109 + 564", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1158" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-248" },{ "correct": false, "text": "454" },{ "correct": true, "text": "455" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-14 + -588", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-603" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-602" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1295" },{ "correct": false, "text": "91" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "311 * -332", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-103329" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-103175" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-103253" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-103252" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-252 * 843", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-212763" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-212109" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-212437" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-212436" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-233 / -133", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1.7518796992481203" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.7518796992481203" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-335.2481203007519" },{ "correct": false, "text": "338.7518796992481" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-576 + 576", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0" },{ "correct": false, "text": "872" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-872" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-203 / -289", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.7024221453287197" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.2975778546712803" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-691.2975778546713" },{ "correct": false, "text": "692.7024221453287" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "571 + 348", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "919" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1336" },{ "correct": false, "text": "918" },{ "correct": false, "text": "502" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-968 / 378", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-860.5608465608466" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-2.560846560846561" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-3.560846560846561" },{ "correct": false, "text": "855.4391534391534" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-909 - 156", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1788" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1066" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1065" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-342" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "514 - 357", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "157" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-180" },{ "correct": false, "text": "156" },{ "correct": false, "text": "494" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "812 + 359", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1074" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1268" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1170" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1171" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "952 + 683", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1065" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1634" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2205" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1635" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-394 + 899", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "807" },{ "correct": true, "text": "505" },{ "correct": false, "text": "203" },{ "correct": false, "text": "504" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "562 + -585", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-23" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-164" },{ "correct": false, "text": "118" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-24" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-742 * -381", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "283320" },{ "correct": false, "text": "282701" },{ "correct": true, "text": "282702" },{ "correct": false, "text": "282084" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-231 + -319", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-789" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-551" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-550" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-311" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-672 - -745", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-72" },{ "correct": false, "text": "218" },{ "correct": true, "text": "73" },{ "correct": false, "text": "72" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "422 / 421", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "382.00237529691213" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.002375296912114" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-379.99762470308787" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.002375296912114022" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "558 * 113", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "63053" },{ "correct": false, "text": "63394" },{ "correct": true, "text": "63054" },{ "correct": false, "text": "62714" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "326 * -513", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-167239" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-167238" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-167083" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-167393" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-53 - -164", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "670" },{ "correct": true, "text": "111" },{ "correct": false, "text": "110" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-448" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "74 / -524", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.1412213740458015" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-819.1412213740458" },{ "correct": false, "text": "818.8587786259542" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.14122137404580154" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "469 * -677", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-317146" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-317513" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-317514" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-317880" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-847 / 333", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-189.54354354354354" },{ "correct": false, "text": "184.45645645645646" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-3.5435435435435436" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-2.5435435435435436" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "754 - 405", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "281" },{ "correct": true, "text": "349" },{ "correct": false, "text": "348" },{ "correct": false, "text": "417" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-134 / -108", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "0.2407407407407407" },{ "correct": false, "text": "923.2407407407408" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-920.7592592592592" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.2407407407407407" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-285 / 398", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "646.2839195979899" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.7160804020100503" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-647.7160804020101" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.7160804020100504" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "850 + 118", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1629" },{ "correct": false, "text": "307" },{ "correct": true, "text": "968" },{ "correct": false, "text": "967" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "628 - -965", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1593" },{ "correct": false, "text": "947" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2239" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1592" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "774 + -561", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "212" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1104" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-678" },{ "correct": true, "text": "213" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "651 / -27", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "634.8888888888889" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-25.11111111111111" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-24.11111111111111" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-683.1111111111111" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-625 / 686", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.9110787172011662" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-24.911078717201168" },{ "correct": false, "text": "23.088921282798832" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.9110787172011663" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-8 / -840", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "168.0095238095238" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.009523809523809525" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-167.9904761904762" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.9904761904761905" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-167 + 186", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-752" },{ "correct": false, "text": "790" },{ "correct": false, "text": "18" },{ "correct": true, "text": "19" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-893 / -437", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "603.0434782608696" },{ "correct": true, "text": "2.0434782608695654" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1.0434782608695654" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-598.9565217391304" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-901 - -72", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-829" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-251" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1407" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-830" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "425 + -173", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "251" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1188" },{ "correct": true, "text": "252" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-684" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-820 + -740", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1663" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1561" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1560" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1457" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-818 * -357", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "291681" },{ "correct": false, "text": "292025" },{ "correct": false, "text": "292371" },{ "correct": true, "text": "292026" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-206 + -129", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-336" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-335" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-324" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-346" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-563 + 717", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "153" },{ "correct": true, "text": "154" },{ "correct": false, "text": "44" },{ "correct": false, "text": "264" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-777 / -775", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-747.9974193548387" },{ "correct": false, "text": "750.0025806451613" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.0025806451612904" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.002580645161290418" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-256 - 948", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-656" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1205" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1752" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1204" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-431 * -456", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "196499" },{ "correct": false, "text": "196535" },{ "correct": true, "text": "196536" },{ "correct": false, "text": "196573" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "965 / 610", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1.5819672131147542" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.5819672131147542" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-666.4180327868852" },{ "correct": false, "text": "669.5819672131148" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-686 - -719", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "33" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-331" },{ "correct": false, "text": "32" },{ "correct": false, "text": "397" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "293 / -519", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-829.5645472061657" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.5645472061657033" },{ "correct": false, "text": "828.4354527938343" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.5645472061657033" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-641 * -305", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "195505" },{ "correct": false, "text": "195504" },{ "correct": false, "text": "195807" },{ "correct": false, "text": "195203" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "114 / -354", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.3220338983050848" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-501.3220338983051" },{ "correct": false, "text": "500.6779661016949" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.3220338983050847" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-201 / -946", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "484.2124735729387" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.7875264270613108" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.2124735729386892" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-483.7875264270613" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "495 + -90", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "404" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-84" },{ "correct": true, "text": "405" },{ "correct": false, "text": "894" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "373 / 811", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "323.45992601726266" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-322.54007398273734" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.5400739827373613" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.4599260172626387" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-114 * 276", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-30590" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-31464" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-32338" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-31465" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "335 + -855", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-521" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-520" },{ "correct": false, "text": "123" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1163" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-730 / -778", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "0.9383033419023136" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-951.0616966580977" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.06169665809768643" },{ "correct": false, "text": "952.9383033419023" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "795 * 516", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "410219" },{ "correct": false, "text": "410237" },{ "correct": false, "text": "410203" },{ "correct": true, "text": "410220" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-650 + 134", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-516" },{ "correct": false, "text": "111" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1143" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-517" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "716 / 457", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "770.5667396061269" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-767.4332603938731" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.5667396061269148" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.5667396061269148" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-660 / -281", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "609.3487544483986" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1.3487544483985765" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-604.6512455516014" },{ "correct": true, "text": "2.3487544483985765" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-11 - 189", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "231" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-631" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-200" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-201" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "799 * -667", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-532934" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-533599" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-532933" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-532267" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "278 * -262", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-73079" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-72837" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-72836" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-72593" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "390 * 440", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "171031" },{ "correct": true, "text": "171600" },{ "correct": false, "text": "172169" },{ "correct": false, "text": "171599" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "142 + -779", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-321" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-638" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-637" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-953" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "789 - -121", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-76" },{ "correct": true, "text": "910" },{ "correct": false, "text": "909" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1896" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-435 - 674", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1110" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-505" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1109" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1713" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "989 + -739", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "249" },{ "correct": false, "text": "917" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-417" },{ "correct": true, "text": "250" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "83 - -701", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "891" },{ "correct": false, "text": "783" },{ "correct": false, "text": "677" },{ "correct": true, "text": "784" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-969 + -229", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1941" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1198" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1199" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-455" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-348 - -665", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "41" },{ "correct": false, "text": "316" },{ "correct": true, "text": "317" },{ "correct": false, "text": "593" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "59 * 692", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "40827" },{ "correct": false, "text": "41378" },{ "correct": true, "text": "40828" },{ "correct": false, "text": "40278" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-679 * -626", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "425054" },{ "correct": false, "text": "425626" },{ "correct": false, "text": "425053" },{ "correct": false, "text": "424482" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-581 - 66", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-647" },{ "correct": false, "text": "349" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1643" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-648" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "180 * 126", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "22679" },{ "correct": false, "text": "21797" },{ "correct": true, "text": "22680" },{ "correct": false, "text": "23563" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "998 * -75", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-74851" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-75460" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-74850" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-74240" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "234 * 544", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "127296" },{ "correct": false, "text": "127295" },{ "correct": false, "text": "128247" },{ "correct": false, "text": "126345" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "782 / -323", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "480.57894736842104" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-2.4210526315789473" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-485.42105263157896" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-3.4210526315789473" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "983 + -932", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "50" },{ "correct": false, "text": "964" },{ "correct": true, "text": "51" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-862" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-180 + -924", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1104" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1967" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-241" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1105" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "113 + 732", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1843" },{ "correct": true, "text": "845" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-153" },{ "correct": false, "text": "844" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "355 / -635", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "595.4409448818898" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.5590551181102361" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-596.5590551181102" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.5590551181102362" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-843 + -165", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1842" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1009" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-174" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1008" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-247 / 956", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.25836820083682" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.2583682008368201" },{ "correct": false, "text": "445.7416317991632" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-446.2583682008368" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-248 / 929", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.2669537136706135" },{ "correct": false, "text": "986.7330462863293" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.26695371367061355" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-987.2669537136707" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-237 / -148", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-610.3986486486486" },{ "correct": false, "text": "613.6013513513514" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.6013513513513513" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.6013513513513513" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-265 * -949", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "250882" },{ "correct": true, "text": "251485" },{ "correct": false, "text": "251484" },{ "correct": false, "text": "252088" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "101 - 458", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-118" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-596" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-357" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-358" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "573 - -805", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1377" },{ "correct": false, "text": "773" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1983" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1378" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-403 / 292", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.38013698630137" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.3801369863013697" },{ "correct": false, "text": "697.6198630136986" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-700.3801369863014" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-227 / 548", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.4142335766423357" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-231.41423357664235" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.4142335766423358" },{ "correct": false, "text": "230.58576642335765" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-754 - 72", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1701" },{ "correct": false, "text": "49" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-827" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-826" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "569 + -63", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "506" },{ "correct": false, "text": "641" },{ "correct": false, "text": "505" },{ "correct": false, "text": "371" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-238 + 893", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "792" },{ "correct": false, "text": "654" },{ "correct": true, "text": "655" },{ "correct": false, "text": "518" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "460 + -191", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "663" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-125" },{ "correct": true, "text": "269" },{ "correct": false, "text": "268" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-481 * 283", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-136037" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-136123" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-136209" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-136124" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "96 * -888", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-85248" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-85059" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-85437" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-85249" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "426 / 428", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.004672897196261627" },{ "correct": false, "text": "199.99532710280374" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.9953271028037384" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-198.00467289719626" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "330 * -436", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-144720" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-143880" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-143040" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-143881" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "978 / -867", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-894.1280276816609" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.1280276816608996" },{ "correct": false, "text": "891.8719723183391" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.1280276816608996" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "14 * 366", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "6063" },{ "correct": false, "text": "5123" },{ "correct": false, "text": "4185" },{ "correct": true, "text": "5124" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-486 / -692", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.29768786127167635" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-424.2976878612717" },{ "correct": false, "text": "425.7023121387283" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.7023121387283237" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "113 / 35", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "2.2285714285714286" },{ "correct": false, "text": "846.2285714285714" },{ "correct": true, "text": "3.2285714285714286" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-839.7714285714286" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "514 + 30", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1359" },{ "correct": false, "text": "543" },{ "correct": true, "text": "544" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-271" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-634 - 599", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-617" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1234" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1849" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1233" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-266 * 129", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-34314" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-34315" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-34058" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-34570" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-132 / 928", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.1422413793103448" },{ "correct": false, "text": "941.8577586206897" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-942.1422413793103" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.14224137931034483" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-533 / 942", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-268.56581740976645" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.5658174097664543" },{ "correct": false, "text": "267.43418259023355" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.5658174097664543" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "14 * -488", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-6043" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-6833" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-6832" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-7621" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-706 - -624", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "158" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-83" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-322" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-82" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "937 - -432", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1368" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1589" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1369" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1149" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-468 * -300", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "141111" },{ "correct": false, "text": "140399" },{ "correct": true, "text": "140400" },{ "correct": false, "text": "139689" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "289 - -464", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "752" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-111" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1617" },{ "correct": true, "text": "753" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-359 + 370", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-749" },{ "correct": false, "text": "10" },{ "correct": false, "text": "771" },{ "correct": true, "text": "11" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-640 + -649", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1523" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1055" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1290" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1289" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-63 / 538", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-71.11710037174721" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.1171003717472119" },{ "correct": false, "text": "70.88289962825279" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.1171003717472119" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "998 * -233", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-231634" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-232535" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-232534" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-233434" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-903 - 820", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-2463" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1724" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-983" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1723" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-914 + -89", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1004" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-428" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1578" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1003" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "562 / 343", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-587.3615160349855" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.6384839650145773" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.6384839650145773" },{ "correct": false, "text": "590.6384839650145" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-245 * 902", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-220022" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-220990" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-220991" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-221958" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "645 * -539", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-347656" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-348100" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-347655" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-347210" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "87 - -464", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "551" },{ "correct": false, "text": "550" },{ "correct": false, "text": "18" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1084" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-753 - -493", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-260" },{ "correct": false, "text": "533" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-261" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1053" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-621 * 820", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-509221" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-509220" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-510172" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-508268" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-537 / 867", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.6193771626297578" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.6193771626297577" },{ "correct": false, "text": "604.3806228373702" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-605.6193771626298" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "907 - 980", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-73" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-74" },{ "correct": false, "text": "652" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-798" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-62 + 887", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "824" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1362" },{ "correct": false, "text": "288" },{ "correct": true, "text": "825" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-222 / -355", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "160.62535211267607" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.6253521126760564" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-159.37464788732393" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.3746478873239436" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "542 * -8", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-4336" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-3928" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-4337" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-4744" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "697 * -601", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-418392" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-418898" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-419402" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-418897" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "965 * 589", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "568056" },{ "correct": false, "text": "568714" },{ "correct": false, "text": "568384" },{ "correct": true, "text": "568385" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "62 - 96", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "640" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-34" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-35" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-708" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "388 + 957", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1345" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2148" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1344" },{ "correct": false, "text": "542" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "131 - -132", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "263" },{ "correct": false, "text": "781" },{ "correct": false, "text": "262" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-255" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-198 - 195", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-461" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-393" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-394" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-325" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-752 * -237", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "177247" },{ "correct": false, "text": "178223" },{ "correct": false, "text": "179201" },{ "correct": true, "text": "178224" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-549 - -670", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "120" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-768" },{ "correct": true, "text": "121" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1010" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-749 * -391", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "292859" },{ "correct": false, "text": "292858" },{ "correct": false, "text": "293311" },{ "correct": false, "text": "292407" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-571 / 235", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "357.5702127659574" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-2.429787234042553" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-3.429787234042553" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-362.4297872340426" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-302 + -345", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-668" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-626" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-648" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-647" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-595 / -761", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "531.7818659658344" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.21813403416557164" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-530.2181340341656" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.7818659658344284" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-3 * -427", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1281" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1321" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1241" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1280" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "573 * 20", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "11459" },{ "correct": true, "text": "11460" },{ "correct": false, "text": "12253" },{ "correct": false, "text": "10667" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "93 + 394", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-334" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1308" },{ "correct": false, "text": "486" },{ "correct": true, "text": "487" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "691 / 740", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.0662162162162162" },{ "correct": false, "text": "407.9337837837838" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-406.0662162162162" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.9337837837837838" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-80 - -66", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-766" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-14" },{ "correct": false, "text": "738" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-15" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-680 + -117", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-798" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-973" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-621" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-797" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-836 - -542", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-294" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-295" },{ "correct": false, "text": "46" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-634" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "88 / -193", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "118.5440414507772" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.455958549222798" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-119.4559585492228" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.45595854922279794" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-55 + 302", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "247" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1055" },{ "correct": false, "text": "246" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-561" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-753 / -74", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-610.8243243243244" },{ "correct": false, "text": "9.175675675675675" },{ "correct": true, "text": "10.175675675675675" },{ "correct": false, "text": "631.1756756756756" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-783 - 594", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1378" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1418" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1377" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1336" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "170 - -691", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1263" },{ "correct": false, "text": "860" },{ "correct": false, "text": "459" },{ "correct": true, "text": "861" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-568 - 55", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1203" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-623" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-43" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-624" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-858 - 859", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1717" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2406" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1718" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1028" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "918 - -914", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1246" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1832" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1831" },{ "correct": false, "text": "2418" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-604 - -772", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "250" },{ "correct": true, "text": "168" },{ "correct": false, "text": "86" },{ "correct": false, "text": "167" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "380 + 906", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1285" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1286" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1542" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1030" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-463 / 867", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.5340253748558248" },{ "correct": false, "text": "921.4659746251442" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-922.5340253748558" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.5340253748558247" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "315 * -438", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-137971" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-138450" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-137490" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-137970" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-11 / 643", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.017107309486780714" },{ "correct": false, "text": "162.9828926905132" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-163.0171073094868" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.0171073094867806" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-105 - 34", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-139" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-48" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-230" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-140" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-407 * -906", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "369393" },{ "correct": false, "text": "368741" },{ "correct": true, "text": "368742" },{ "correct": false, "text": "368091" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-485 / -96", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-598.9479166666666" },{ "correct": true, "text": "5.052083333333333" },{ "correct": false, "text": "4.052083333333333" },{ "correct": false, "text": "609.0520833333334" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "819 / -158", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "692.8164556962025" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-6.1835443037974684" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-5.1835443037974684" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-703.1835443037975" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "715 + 965", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "2334" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1679" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1026" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1680" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-234 - 218", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-989" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-452" },{ "correct": false, "text": "85" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-453" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "974 / -625", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "156.4416" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.5584" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-159.5584" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.5584" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "867 + -789", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "78" },{ "correct": false, "text": "310" },{ "correct": false, "text": "77" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-154" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-331 + 46", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1190" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-286" },{ "correct": false, "text": "620" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-285" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-130 / -344", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "13.377906976744185" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-12.622093023255815" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.37790697674418605" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.622093023255814" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "451 - 494", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-351" },{ "correct": false, "text": "265" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-43" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-44" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-865 - -919", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "53" },{ "correct": false, "text": "992" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-884" },{ "correct": true, "text": "54" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-241 / -598", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.5969899665551839" },{ "correct": false, "text": "477.40301003344484" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-476.59698996655516" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.40301003344481606" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-994 - 400", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1395" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1744" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1044" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1394" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "746 - -180", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "926" },{ "correct": false, "text": "230" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1622" },{ "correct": false, "text": "925" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "521 + 989", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1714" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1509" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1510" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1306" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-116 / -87", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "0.33333333333333326" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.3333333333333333" },{ "correct": false, "text": "186.33333333333334" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-183.66666666666666" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "944 - 828", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-498" },{ "correct": true, "text": "116" },{ "correct": false, "text": "115" },{ "correct": false, "text": "730" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-462 + -932", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1395" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-968" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1820" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1394" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-151 + 539", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "388" },{ "correct": false, "text": "424" },{ "correct": false, "text": "352" },{ "correct": false, "text": "387" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-98 / -57", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-41.280701754385966" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.7192982456140351" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.719298245614035" },{ "correct": false, "text": "44.719298245614034" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "946 - 229", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "938" },{ "correct": false, "text": "716" },{ "correct": false, "text": "496" },{ "correct": true, "text": "717" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "752 - -934", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1750" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1622" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1685" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1686" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "274 / 655", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-412.58167938931297" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.581679389312977" },{ "correct": false, "text": "413.41832061068703" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.4183206106870229" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "248 * 366", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "90768" },{ "correct": false, "text": "90230" },{ "correct": false, "text": "91306" },{ "correct": false, "text": "90767" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-156 / 90", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.7333333333333334" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-669.7333333333333" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.7333333333333334" },{ "correct": false, "text": "666.2666666666667" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-60 / -970", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "828.0618556701031" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.9381443298969072" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.061855670103092786" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-827.9381443298969" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-2 - -988", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "662" },{ "correct": true, "text": "986" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1310" },{ "correct": false, "text": "985" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-686 + 375", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-311" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-312" },{ "correct": false, "text": "250" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-872" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-93 * -631", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "58682" },{ "correct": false, "text": "57828" },{ "correct": false, "text": "59538" },{ "correct": true, "text": "58683" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-731 * 938", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-685678" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-685679" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-685680" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-685676" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-201 / -343", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-647.4139941690962" },{ "correct": false, "text": "648.5860058309038" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.5860058309037901" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.4139941690962099" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-975 * -944", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "920400" },{ "correct": false, "text": "920577" },{ "correct": false, "text": "920399" },{ "correct": false, "text": "920223" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "350 - -114", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "464" },{ "correct": false, "text": "463" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-480" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1408" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-825 * -448", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "370221" },{ "correct": false, "text": "369599" },{ "correct": true, "text": "369600" },{ "correct": false, "text": "368979" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "388 + -473", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-323" },{ "correct": false, "text": "153" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-85" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-86" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-458 - -120", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-339" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-325" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-338" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-351" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "312 / -327", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.9541284403669725" },{ "correct": false, "text": "272.04587155963304" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-273.95412844036696" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.9541284403669725" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "269 * -762", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-205090" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-204979" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-204978" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-204866" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "340 / 269", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-598.7360594795539" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.2639405204460967" },{ "correct": false, "text": "601.2639405204461" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1.2639405204460967" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-396 / 521", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.7600767754318618" },{ "correct": false, "text": "48.23992322456814" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.7600767754318618" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-49.76007677543186" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "987 - -734", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "2075" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1721" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1720" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1367" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "813 + -357", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "455" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1014" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-102" },{ "correct": true, "text": "456" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-128 + 830", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "349" },{ "correct": false, "text": "701" },{ "correct": true, "text": "702" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1055" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "493 + 371", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "864" },{ "correct": false, "text": "27" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1701" },{ "correct": false, "text": "863" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "564 + 191", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1611" },{ "correct": false, "text": "754" },{ "correct": true, "text": "755" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-101" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-532 + 536", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "4" },{ "correct": false, "text": "3" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-345" },{ "correct": false, "text": "353" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "28 * 273", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "7370" },{ "correct": false, "text": "7918" },{ "correct": true, "text": "7644" },{ "correct": false, "text": "7643" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-25 / -967", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "739.0258531540848" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-0.9741468459152016" },{ "correct": true, "text": "0.025853154084798345" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-738.9741468459152" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "725 * 220", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "160253" },{ "correct": true, "text": "159500" },{ "correct": false, "text": "159499" },{ "correct": false, "text": "158747" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "320 - 828", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-871" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-145" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-509" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-508" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-665 - 580", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-875" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1246" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1245" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1615" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "815 + -371", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "444" },{ "correct": false, "text": "389" },{ "correct": false, "text": "443" },{ "correct": false, "text": "499" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "273 + -746", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1224" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-473" },{ "correct": false, "text": "278" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-474" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "966 - 728", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "238" },{ "correct": false, "text": "967" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-491" },{ "correct": false, "text": "237" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "810 / -958", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "209.1544885177453" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-210.8455114822547" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.8455114822546972" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.8455114822546973" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-693 / -590", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1.1745762711864407" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-172.82542372881355" },{ "correct": false, "text": "175.17457627118645" },{ "correct": false, "text": "0.1745762711864407" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-740 * -896", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "663040" },{ "correct": false, "text": "663039" },{ "correct": false, "text": "662219" },{ "correct": false, "text": "663861" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "918 * -618", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-567379" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-567325" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-567324" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-567269" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-99 - -324", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "225" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-610" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1060" },{ "correct": false, "text": "224" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "991 + 78", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1069" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1266" },{ "correct": false, "text": "872" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1068" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "19 + 769", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "371" },{ "correct": false, "text": "787" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1205" },{ "correct": true, "text": "788" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "0 + 902", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1451" },{ "correct": true, "text": "902" },{ "correct": false, "text": "901" },{ "correct": false, "text": "353" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-56 - 749", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-667" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-943" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-805" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-806" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-738 / 997", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-0.7402206619859579" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1.740220661985958" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-781.740220661986" },{ "correct": false, "text": "780.259779338014" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "954 / -537", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-2.776536312849162" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-409.77653631284915" },{ "correct": false, "text": "406.22346368715085" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1.776536312849162" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "985 - 829", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "155" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1024" },{ "correct": true, "text": "156" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-712" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-972 * -160", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "154860" },{ "correct": true, "text": "155520" },{ "correct": false, "text": "155519" },{ "correct": false, "text": "156180" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "466 + -474", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-287" },{ "correct": false, "text": "271" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-9" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-8" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-357 * -339", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "121023" },{ "correct": false, "text": "120580" },{ "correct": false, "text": "121022" },{ "correct": false, "text": "121466" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-669 - -942", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-591" },{ "correct": false, "text": "272" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1137" },{ "correct": true, "text": "273" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-819 + -626", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1446" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1445" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1983" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-907" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "141 - 377", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1218" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-237" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-236" },{ "correct": false, "text": "746" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-762 + -700", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-977" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1462" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1947" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1463" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "706 + -876", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-760" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-170" },{ "correct": false, "text": "420" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-171" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-777 + -869", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-849" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1647" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-2443" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1646" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "453 + 282", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "735" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-187" },{ "correct": false, "text": "734" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1657" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-738 - -125", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-614" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1207" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-19" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-613" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "686 + 381", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "1067" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1582" },{ "correct": false, "text": "552" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1066" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "835 - 17", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "818" },{ "correct": false, "text": "804" },{ "correct": false, "text": "832" },{ "correct": false, "text": "817" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-115 - 456", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-325" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-817" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-571" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-572" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-318 * -868", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "276024" },{ "correct": false, "text": "276048" },{ "correct": false, "text": "276023" },{ "correct": false, "text": "276000" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "566 - 440", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-413" },{ "correct": true, "text": "126" },{ "correct": false, "text": "665" },{ "correct": false, "text": "125" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "279 - 377", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-99" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-161" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-98" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-35" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "2 + -679", "answers": [{ "correct": true, "text": "-677" },{ "correct": false, "text": "272" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-678" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1626" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "515 + 353", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "333" },{ "correct": true, "text": "868" },{ "correct": false, "text": "867" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1403" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "879 - -309", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1197" },{ "correct": true, "text": "1188" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1179" },{ "correct": false, "text": "1187" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-330 - 57", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "180" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-387" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-388" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-954" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "502 - -370", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "871" },{ "correct": true, "text": "872" },{ "correct": false, "text": "841" },{ "correct": false, "text": "903" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "732 / -334", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-499.19161676646706" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-3.191616766467066" },{ "correct": false, "text": "494.80838323353294" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-2.191616766467066" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-534 * 454", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-242373" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-242437" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-242499" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-242436" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "121 + 561", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "1060" },{ "correct": true, "text": "682" },{ "correct": false, "text": "681" },{ "correct": false, "text": "304" }] },{ "category": "Math", "question": "-275 - 963", "answers": [{ "correct": false, "text": "-1239" },{ "correct": true, "text": "-1238" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-1759" },{ "correct": false, "text": "-717" }] }]
